From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, true scepticality goes unfold.
D-dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Sly for your wake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's old, deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Then Sly for your wake, can't ston't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream
what's up? I'm good lighting tonight. Hi, what's up? Nice to see you. You told
Chanda come over? Okay, cool. Yeah, I just did a quick tiktok until eight o'clock
tonight. It went really well. I got a bunch of called diamonds. I guess it's
It's that I made like picture sense today, because but it's pretty cool. No, I just uh
I said a quick quick live over there and
It's fun. It gets I get to do more terror over there than I do over here. And so
here it's like people like to uh
Okay, so anyway, it's messy Monday, so why don't I just go ahead and open the panel tonight? Why not?
Let's make it messy.
If I do one day a week, I'll just do one day a week.
Open panels, free, non-sponsored.
But still, if you'd like to have the panel sponsored,
you can always donate to have your advertisement put
on the banner.
There we go.
But I'll open it up.
OK.
I'm saying hi Trix.
Hi.
Yes, they're fine, Jamie.
Trixie.
There's Lola over there.
Lola's here.
Yeah.
So I got a really good dinner coming.
I got the same place I ordered last time
because it's like 75% off.
So I'm getting like a s'mores shake again
with the Baileys in it like I had last time.
I'm getting,
they had to order guacamole to get the bill right.
So it's like it was a certain right amount like I said, I got a so I'll put that on the cheeseburger. I have a cheeseburger
Hi rude
There's Rudy over here. Hi
my attention
He loves attention. Oh, I can I hug him? Yes
There's something called the backyard cheeseburger with guacamole. I
What else did I get?
The Bailey's more shake. It's really good
Yeah, it comes out to like 20 bucks, which is like better than anything else like the 20 bucks delivery. That's pretty cool
So it should be good. I
Did my finally got my return at Whole Foods. I'm getting my stuff stuff done. So
Really happy. Everything's going good. Hi guys got Jamie. Hey Bulbasack, please gain weight. You hate the concentration
Oh, I know I'm skinny. I'm trying to gain some weight though. Oh
This is how I've always been though
Full the sack that's not very nice come on
But it's okay. I've I've heard that many times
She had a good appetite. I'm a good appetite tonight. I'm gonna scarf down this food and we'll see how long I can stay up
But I might have a shorter night might just be up for a few hours tonight
I mean, really crazy dreams, like there's one time a year where I have these crazy dreams.
Hi, we're back, Christine, yes.
I said I'd be back at eight, and so I got some dinner on the way, and I got some errands
done, and feeling good, did a quick TikTok.
At least gain 10 pounds. Okay. I need someone to cook for me. I really do. I need like a I need like an Italian grandmother here
You know, hi Yvonne. How are you?
But I do notice like I look I look better on film tonight. They don't look as kind of scary. I
Think I have good lighting right now. I think this is perfect lighting with my little my alien
The kitty cat. Hi. Nice to see you
It's really cool, huh? That's spunky got me that a beautiful neon sign. It's the coolest neon sign ever
Also, I have some cars. Let's see Christine. Yeah, but remember you have as a
Asmikos people too. Yep, Yvonne a punch you
Let's see, it's a cute name you get my glasses on
So I have a really good dinner coming and then I'll hang out. Yeah, but I'll open up the panel for everybody tonight
we'll see I'm not in a I'm in a pretty good mood and
So everyone feel free to come up. I'll post the link at pin it
If you would like to sponsor the panel
It's always welcome
And
Let's see, I think we're
Is Yvonne have a wrench is Yvonne a one wrench
I'm gonna pin the link but I consider it she's
It's like if there are some people that
Well, you know she has a class she has a classic trollish name, but hey, what's up?
So this is what Gotti put Gotti said. Oh, he found me. He said he found what I look like
There's the most hipster man in the world
God, he's got he said he found a video of me does kind of look like me though, huh? I need to make a beard like that
Your controversial it's up to you. You don't mind being wait. Well, it's just like it's just like would you like, you know, I know you're controversial, but
Would you like, you know, stick up for the show kind of thing
Like everyone, okay, we've been my link and I'll consider it
Just try to all I ask is just try to have my back like on other chats
It's fine. It's not my show is like, you know, it's like not only donations of you know
people donate or donate or there's certain monetized parts of the channel too
But you know, also just being here supporting the chat, you know, I appreciate everything
Yeah, I'll try I'll think Jamie's word for it because Jamie's top mod but okay, there's
Hopefully joker comes soon and also
Oh, hold on
I got a guy that got some new carbs in the mail
If I see my keys, I'll go run and get them. I see my keys on the table. Let me see
Okay, I'll be right back
Think I was a false alarm. Oh
Like all the way down to my mailbox. Hey, what's up? Oh
Feels gay. Oh shoot
Have a nice dinner coming though. What did I get today? I got a really cool soap. I want to show you guys
Okay, well I got this this is my vacuum your vacuum cleaner
Teemu
There's like 20 something bucks
But I got this really good soap too
Take a special kind of soap, but I don't see it around
How are we doing? Let me see
Clean off my glasses
Hi vanguard
Psychian all pronouns
Okay, come on up and
You everyone's welcome on tonight. It's messy Monday, so
Keep it messy
Yeah, team moves got some good stuff. I got this. It's like it's a vacuum and you just need a vacuum
It looks like a pretty good one
For just like 20 something bucks
Yeah, hey, hey Rudy Rudy's here. Hey kitty cats
You miss pagey pagey was here last night. Did you see page last night? So she's here
Hello, hello there, so you're it. Hello, my friend. Oh
Here is this it. Yeah, I got this I got this soap. It's called it's called protection and it's OB
It says only way protection so it's purifying
cleansing obstacle healing
So it's like a magical soap, I guess
Oh, holy we oh dear that sounds very yeah, holy way
That's African or something. I wonder where it's from. I don't know much about it
You would heard of it Obi-Wan Obi-Wan Kenobi, Obi
No
Before we crack on can I just say something about me coming on your channel? Yeah
I have found you drop people like a hot piece of soap or a used condom when the conversation
is finished and you go on to the next things, it's a channel and that's nothing to do with
me.
I'm just giving you a...
an experience of a YouTube interaction of somebody who goes on the many panels
how have come about your panel?
But you do drop people like Hot Potatoes and the pronouns hidden there.
I do have a really like a lot of trolls and so if it gets too trollish or sometimes it just gets like, you know
Yeah, but the other day I was talking to alexander mayors making conversation between you and her
But you dropped us both
And i didn't drop alexandra. I didn't drop alexandra. I'm glad you're burning your white sage
Do I
Do I really vitrify the fact that you have to burn siege because the vanguard's here?
Well, I mean, it's just like, I'm opening the show, I'm like, you know, just cleansing the panel.
Hey Janet, how are you? Hi everybody. Yeah, so...
All right, can you do me a fear app? Yeah promise
Promise not to drop me unless I'm being a dick in the future
Okay, I'll try I'll try but you know I do like you know
Sometimes I get out impulses you also get paid to drop people don't yeah. Yeah
Okay, we have random random guy coming up. Hold on. Yeah
All right, we got a chaperone. I can come on now. So, uh, the reason he drops you off too because you're fucking boring
what would you know about boring
I eat also if you annoy him
or you're boring or it's a combination of the both you're fucking done
so you're not scared to do it either
that's why I respect about him he's done it to me a few times I'm not saying I'm immune to it
but that's what it was
yeah but no fuck
are you seeing are you seeing your IRL circle jacket too
no just let you know like it's a fact
Yeah, man, we all know the fact the fact is
He's paid to do stuff. He does stuff because he gets money, but anyway, but did you pay him yesterday to be on or?
I don't pay anybody
There's your answer right there. No one has to pay to be on
Yeah, I got you on that, but yeah
The panel should be sponsored like a sponsor, but I'm doing it's messy Monday
So I'm doing a free panel tonight and yeah, man. Yeah, man, but I don't pay anybody. That's why I only come up
Well, then you have to you know, you're and you I might you know kick you off if I feel like
It's like I gotta produce the show and you know, it's like I don't know
But I didn't kick off Alexandra Alexandra is a great guest and I would I'm certainly didn't kick her off. So, you know
Yeah, I've talked to her many times in the past, you know
Mm-hmm. Yeah, she's gorgeous too. Like I saw her like on the bikini contest at Christine too
I think Christine and Alexander Mayer
You know, it's summer they won the bikini contest, but you know, I appreciate everybody
So have you ever met Alicia Jordana and Andy Dick before?
Have I met them? No, I mean, I've you know, I just I've talked to her on the phone many times
and I've read tarot cards for her and
Haven't I haven't been on her show in a few weeks
I do talk to her producer to her producer sometimes watches this show, but it doesn't really talk in the chat
But yeah, and that any dick thing happened way before I was around, but yeah, he's in the pretty much the area the baby suits
Yeah, I saw I saw a little replay of the
BD to but but also yeah beat his show also it is syndicated like mine is on rumble if you ever like, you know
Because she deletes a lot of her stuff, you know, yeah
Well, for this indication, I don't make anything, but all I do is have my show put on rumble.
And so it's like interesting.
So because it's not attached to me, I can never get my account banned or anything for
it.
But so they can, when I get poor bomb and everything, I delete the whole episode.
It's going to be still up there.
And so it kind of has the archive of my shows for, you know, so that's pretty nice.
Well, maybe I can learn, maybe I can learn a few things or two from you's bunch of fucking
There's money to be made somewhere
Well, it's like, you know, it's like you offer it's basically just offers offer
You have monetization avenues and people will take advantage of them, you know, it's like and then if you have the certain
You're certain kind of you know audience established
Yeah, but I would never sell my soul. I would never sell my soul for financial gain
Well, everyone has to make a living somehow, you know, it's like and so what what is it what's what's what's worse than one other way
It's like as long as you're not stealing
Working for 11 hours a
Yeah, manual labor
Yeah, manual people work manual labor and then there's ways of there's ways to
Do what you your dream is, you know, there's ways to make your dreams come true
This is my dream and it's like I'm pouring a lot of love it love energy and
It's not always easy it's not always going to be easy, you know, it's like
But anyway, I'm trying my best
I get it I get it but it's a form of prostitution really in a modern world
I'm not sent in for you psyche. I'm what do you do, sir?
What can I address you as what's your what's your name Baldwin baby? No, that's not you. What's your fucking? Oh, sorry
Sorry, he is a he's Vanguard. Oh Vanguard. Okay, Vanguard indeed. What do you do?
What did I do? I'm a retired
Ex-military person. How are you doing? Wait, wait, wait, what?
I'm an ex-retired
Ex-military person. Oh, really? How are you doing? Yeah, so you just worked in the military your entire life?
Yes, what did you do in the military British real forces?
What I did in the military I shoveled shit all day long
Okay
Well, that process is that prostitution to your country because you know for it, you know, it's a no it's like but
Neither is what I do prostitution or what people at stream do is do so. It's not a very apt comparison
prostitution is literally like you know opening your legs and like
Having a random stranger, you know inside of you
well, basically isn't that the left or the right's an
absolute power of the media these days
The media? The media is powerful, but it's a way to just have a message put out to multiple
people at one time. And so it's also we have people have power over the media now, too,
instead of just the networks, you know, before it was just a network program and everything
we watched.
Now may I just respond may I just respond to that? Yes, I'm ex-military
I've been retired for quite a few years, but I'm over half a century year old
But I served in the household cavalry of the British army. I served Her Majesty the Queen
so
Let's just hear this the world is what it is
and the way people receive it, all I can see is I'm an absolute person that says,
this is all bullshit, you know what I mean?
Yeah, well, there's that, there's that upset,
does that upset the Circle Jerk narrative at all?
I apologize, it does, I, I apologize.
Like that well not at all, but it's like I don't even know what you're really talking about you're just kind of rambling
You're here on the panel, too. I don't get it. You're you're in it. You're in it
Do you know what's the household Cavalry? Oh, I?
Have no fucking idea. I'm not gonna lie to you. No, what is that?
You do have no idea what the household
Cavalry is like a housekeeper. It's like all the step of the house. Yeah, you're a maid
You wear that little fucking front dress like what'd you do like I
Got my food guys my food here right there. Do we get kicked? Thank God you're here
It's all what the fuck is this I'm grabbing my food. Hold on one second. Oh, okay. Yeah, you're the grim reaper
This guy
the
But anyway
You might see Donald Trump interfere with the household cavity this weekend. Yeah, whatever
So
You got you got people like talk about global warming and you gotta save the planet and fucking bunch of hippies, right?
It's more of a leftist thing
But it's always like the leftists want to be like, I don't want to get political, but it's always like the leftists want to say, oh my god, you're so untraveled, but listen, don't you think that that's polluting the planet with all that flying that you do?
the
Me am I right am I wrong I did not mean to upset yet. It was just upset dude. I'm just having a I'm having a debate
I'm having a go a ghost
Question I apologize a direct question. Oops. Yeah. Well, let's go back to it. Okay, so I've been to Florida
North Carolina
Where's that one the fuck it's a real shitty city by site. What the fuck is that dude?
I've been there. I see you know, I explored the city. I saw people hanging around on benches shooting fucking heroin
In the middle of like today a bunch of tents
Bunch of tents people living in tents in Denver, Colorado. It was it was horrendous. Absolutely horrendous. What a shitty fucking place
Anyway, that one that must be cold in the winter
It must be real cold in the winter. Yeah, it was hot in the summer because you're you're you're you're higher up
The elevation is higher so you're closer to the Sun
Whoa, it was hot there. Whoa
Hey psych, you ever been to Denver?
No, I've never been in Denver, but I know about the Denver Airport. It's like a very occultish airport. Oh, yeah
I like this. Yeah, there's quarantine. Yeah, I saw that really the devil the fucking horse
It's a blue horse named Lucifer. Yes
Have you seen the actual airport not the airport, but the
Airfields almost look like a swastika. Yeah, I've seen that too
I've seen that. I've seen the murals that were inside of there of like, you know, NAZI, you know, guards and
People don't show us. I want to see yeah, I can show you
So, yeah, this is the dead. They had this very famous artist. He's like a South American artist. They had I think these have been painted over since then too, but
It's all the new world order isn't it's like new world order is
Okay, so here's it says the murals they were made by Leo Tanguma and
I kind of might be a little bit difficult to see I can maybe I can
upload
Have you heard about the miles of tunnels underneath the airport?
So yeah, the miles of tunnels underground the dumps the deep underground
Military bases. It's kind of hard to see. I'm actually I might try to get some photos
And I'll I can attach them to the to the stream. Hold on. I'll be right back
So vanguard I've been Virgin Islands, Ohio
West Virginia
Kentucky all kinds of girls
Never been to Texas
It's not a nice to meet your random guy all his leaves work. Why have you traveled to?
Um, I've been mostly all over Europe. I've been to Southeast Asia
I've been to
Canardia, you know where canardia is now
I've also been to the murica fuck yeah
You've been America
Yeah, man. I've been Murica. I just like Murica. Murica was very Vegas.
What did you just do right there? Why don't I always do that?
Because I'm the vanguard. I love it.
This this was more Donald Trump, but Murica was decent back then. I mean come on.
OK, um
Yeah
So anyway, I don't mean I don't mean to be facetious. I mean
What the fuck it's a beautiful country
Wait, wait a second. What's the British? You said you were a British housemaid and the art like what is what is that?
What do you say?
What?
What does housemaids riding horses with swords in armor?
No, just tell me what it can you explain cuz I don't fucking know I'm not well traveled man. What did you say you were?
That's the household Calvary. Oh, yeah household Calvary. What is that?
That's exactly what my avatar is
Okay
Do I have to like Google it or something or do I care anymore? I'm just asking man
There are two regiments of the household cavalry, there are seven regiments of the household, five a foot, two of horse.
In my regiment, and I was part of it, called the Blues and Royals, which are the second part of the household cavalry, mounted cavalry of the household.
Yeah, my god, you wrote trash
They say fair enough there were a trash you're a trash
Fair enough
Yeah, I looked it up I looked it up on
Fucking
What's it called? I looked it up on Wikipedia. Um, it looks kind of serious, huh? Yes
Yeah, that's cool. Yeah, good for you
Yeah, but but we also
Drive tanks, you know what tanks are tanks. Yeah
We drive challenges
No, there's no infantry when you're Calvary Calvary
But anyway
Thank you. Tell tell me a story
Which story would you like to hear?
Pick one
Would you like to hear the story when the Berlin Wall fell?
No, that's kind of boring
What you are you saying you weren't alive when the I think I want yet. Yeah, I was I was
Wait, who was that fucking rock store that was like singing what was that dude's name?
Like American singer he was kind of attached to the Berlin Wall
Are you talking about David Hasselhoff, right?
Ha
How'd that even fucking come about? What is that David Hasselhoff in the Berlin wall?
I believe he dropped these burger from the Berlin wall at one thing
Yeah, oh he performed there, okay New Year's Eve
Do you think that's what
Cause it's yeah, he actually is huge in Germany. Yes. He is yes
Big time I don't know why but he is yeah, it was David Hassel off
So if I said gong park to you which song would that remind you of running that
Say it again
Donkey park which song without a menu of donkey park
No, no donkey gunky
gunky
I don't know dude. I'm not a huge. Uh, David Hasselhoff fan. Oh, he was an actor
It's got fuck all
He's in Germany. He's a singer in Germany
Famous German singer, isn't he?
I guarantee if you played some David Hasseloff, it would ring a bell. It would ring a bell for not my life
It's broken the window by the edge
It's a Kevin the H2
The door has a lot of fear anyway, I served in Germany by the way
Hmm
And he also been to many American px's the big px
You know what a px is?
It's the American
Why is he laughing psych? Why is this guy laughing? He's nuts
Hello there some month
Anyway, the big PX is your you know PX is where you go buy your chocolate your things
Etc. Your cigarettes things like that the big PX
The land of the big PX
Do you run them guy?
I'll be honest with you did I was browsing towards and David has to hop on iTunes
I don't recognize any of the any of these fucking songs
It's nothing well, it means nothing to me
David Hasselhoff has nothing to do with a gunky park. Yeah, but I'm stuck dude. Once you get on one topic
I I can't move away from it. Yeah, I got stuck on David Hasselhoff. He was a German singer
Yeah, but he sucks dude. I don't know anything about this guy. I mean I heard his name. Be watch. I'm browsing through his songs right now trying to like
None of them ring a fucking bell. So like, yeah, I don't know
There was a time when he was like drunk at home and eating and she's burger on the floor
And I got her on that was awesome and his daughter said what?
He got drunk one night the idiot she's burger on the floor, and he's like, ah
He's a girl and she's like this is what you're like when you drink
What a nightmare and then I got out to everybody
Maybe that'll help greatest hits
Well, hey, so random guy. What do you call a quarter pound of cheese in France?
It's not the uh, it's not the Royale, what the fuck is it called again?
Royale with cheese, Pulp Fiction. What are you laughing? What's so funny?
You got it right Royale with cheese. Yeah, it's in Pulp Fiction. It's a famous movie
It's a great movie
Well, it's a great movie. Do you ever see Pulp Fiction Vanguard?
Why would I mention it? I haven't seen Pulp Fiction. Can I actually question your logic?
I've not seen it. Why would I mention it?
Sorry. Yeah, he mentioned it without mentioning it. Yeah, it's like, you know, it's like you might have just been like wondering
Cuz of course, of course, I'm random guys seen Pulp Fiction everyone
Pulp Fiction America
Yeah, but I'm a little shocked right now because I'm like I'm trying to like
See if I recognize any David Hasselhoff song, but I just don't
Don't you've never you've never recognized the devil
No, it's not working
Right
Go go put in Google David Hasselhoff German songs, and I believe you'll find something
So you in Chinese pot no, this is like French fries with like some kind of sauce
Yeah
You're on a Vanguard and Bannum guy
Yeah, man, but anyway, my apologies. I thought that you were eating out with Chinese noodle box my apologies, but
Very good
Like these french fries that are like in some kind of sauce with like onions and shit
Oh, right. So it's loaded. It's loaded fries with like bacon sauce. It's like a baked potato. Yeah, baby's bacon in it. What's up?
This s'mores s'mores milkshake with with the with the
Bailey's in it
You got Bailey's Irish cream in it. Nice one shot of Bailey's in it. Yeah
Mm-hmm very good, and I'm burger to eat it was all under 20 bucks pretty good deal
$20
Delivered as well. Yeah
Okay, so this is the Tom flat guys. I'm kind of remembering Tom flash. He's well. He's not able to come back yet
But uh, what am I seeing? It looks like he's
Pornographic something or other is that real it looks fake hold on Tom. What's going on here? I've heard I've heard about you
Let's running and why are you really from the people podcast? I
Don't know what I'm looking at
Yes, running and why with a fucking what flag with the under name the people podcasts
Really fuck
Are you really from the people pockets? Yeah, I've ever said the people podcast what?
Okay, yeah guys Tom flash was the one that do has had that really perverted stuff, right?
Yes vanguard you were you interested in um, do you like the channel or something?
Well, I've come across it recently, but I didn't know it was like
Alias running in wire
Whatever flag is it Colombian? No, it's not Colombian. No, it's not Puerto Rican
Yeah, man fair playmate, I'm just taking the nickel, but I'm just saying I've come across your
Um channel recently. Yeah. Yeah, I'm on February. Nice to meet you. Welcome. I'm like, nice to meet you. We welcome anybody on the panel. Yeah. If you want to come up, you will come up. Nice to meet you, fellow. Nice to meet you, too. Yeah. Well, everyone's, everyone's welcome tonight. It's an open panel tonight, so.
Vanguard's just retired. So, you know, I think I kind of understand why you're going on
Thank you, I know sorry last night was kind of crazy, right?
Like we just had a bunch of like I had a bunch of like weird people coming up and like
Oh, I was there. Yes. I was there. I was there was my mm-hmm. I made a random appearance for like 30 seconds
mmm
But the Tom Flash person just came backstage and was like there's something like it was like his lower body or something
He's like legs on a like without I don't know
I don't know if I was seeing pornography or what but it seemed to seem like strange and I remember if he pooped
He was on the other night and did something
Pretty much unforgivable. So
Under that name, I don't know then they then I didn't see that person somewhere else say. Oh, yeah
I'm trying to take down this channel. I'm not sure if you're saying
Well, Tom flush is a bit bit peculiar
In a person really isn't he's already peculiar
Mm-hmm reminds me of like let me see like
Something like a mad scientist or something
Yeah, has the trader case you've been around he said he was planning something for psyche
He was stupid and smug about it
Yeah, he's probably gone to Emma's and like he thinks that like he's talked to people in her discord or something like that
He thinks there's gonna be some kind of I don't know lame
He's actually lame. I'm running out of material. I do have to say
to the uh chat or whatever i know that vanguard might be a little bit like boring to listen to but
it like talking to him on a panel is just really odd and it's slightly interesting it's really odd
and slightly interesting you don't know what you're doing it's like a fucking it just confuses you
but i suggest you try it yeah yeah without a mouse do you yeah you confused me all right see you
Okay, so anyway, KZ is still trying to get on the panel and stuff under different names
and stuff.
I can always tell who it is because it's like...
I don't know people are just pretty
Yeah, I'm not allowed to get Fred Alastair here
He's he's a what are you one of her like just a monk flying monkeys just like sent to like make sure and take right down
Anything I say and bring it back to her or something like that. Why are you so obsessed like he'd ever come?
He never shows up until I say her name and I am allowed to say her name
My name is not allowed in her chat, but I'm allowed to say anybody's name. You know, I want to it's called free speech. I
Didn't slander anybody
And talk about anybody I want
Fred Alastair
So maybe I should keep my mouth shut and read a bit more of the chat
But I only see the chat on YouTube not on discord and all the other platform
Oh, you're mad we need a new friend. Oh, so yeah, we're mad you made a new friend. Oh my gosh
Go report back to her go report back to her. It'll fly in monkey
Go on. Okay. So anyway, I did get a picture of the of that. We were just talking about the
Hold on, not that one. Hold on.
What?
Let's see. Hold on.
I'll leave some stuff. Hold on.
Uh-oh.
Wow. I do love that fucking...
Lovely.
It's South American.
What?
Here. Look at this. Look at this stuff.
These are the Denver Airport. We were just discussing.
So here's some Denver Airport. This is the horse named Lucifer.
Oh, yeah, man. I know that one. But can you show the people the layout of the the landing fields, please?
I don't want to put that up, but I'll show you this is another thing where she's like, you know
Everything's on fire the kids are all like they're horrified and like there's like a penguin in a box and all this kind of stuff
Yeah, man, it's very biblical. It's very
in times in it can you show the one where everybody's getting killed by soldiers
no I can't find that one but you know what it was a little bit too much for the airport too because
they didn't have they painted over those murals with like other stuff that's less controversial
It's kind of like looks more normal, but at one time and there's also this gargoyle thing
There's like a gargoyle and they put like a little voice box in the gargoyle and had it's a gargoyle in the suitcase
And so there's like that and they made it talk and there's like a prank where they made it talk
I think they play into the they play into like the New World thing a little bit too
I don't know, but they do have underground underground DUM bees which are deep underground military bases
The demon horse cook his name is Blucifer
But we can mention the extensive groundworks that were played and excavated with the Denver Airport.
Why it was so delayed for so long.
Well, why was it what happened?
You're American, you're miracle. You tell me.
Don't know it's like it said was delayed because they I mean they're doing the bases underground bases. I guess right
Extensive on the ground
excavation
Well, everyone's welcome up, we're just talking about some interesting stuff
Having my dinner. I don't mean to be offensive, but
I'm only talking about what the internet says the internet says that down the
airport is very suspicious congratulations spunky drop your
channel so everyone can subscribe and check out your show if spunky says she's
going live for the first time tomorrow night at 10 30 so that's awesome
If you want me to leave, just ask me. I'll leave.
No, you're fine. You're fine. You're fine tonight.
We're just having a nice calm night.
I'm just, you know, having these fries and oh my god,
there's also these jalapeno poppers they have.
Oh my gosh, I'm just going to be stuck.
Jalapeno, nacho cheese, proper cheddar cheese,
bacon bits, fucking turkey bits,
There's the burger it looks pretty good. Is it wagyu burger smashed at that?
It does look nice by the way. Can I have a bite?
He's like a he's like a he's like a backyard barbecue burger.
Have you ever had a wagyu burger?
Well, it says like wagyu is that like is that like Kobe beef, which is like this the most tender beef
The wagyu is like another kind of like
You know what this is worse milkshake, it's very uh, it's more as milkshake
Just asking if you ever had a wagyu burger, I'm sure I have we have a lot of Japanese
Japanese like places around here that will serve that kind of thing
um
Of course, but I might attempt Japanese. I mostly eat sushi, you know
It has to be like it on the menu of a another restaurant
I prefer steaks. I like steaks
May I apologize part?
Yes, the people's podcast left because he does no connection. I do apologize for people's podcasts
Are you down my list? Yes. Sorry. Sorry. I quite like the people's
Podcasts to be honest. Mm-hmm. Well, I don't think there is is the people's podcast still around
I think that they might be on a backup channel right now
Am I right?
I'm just making sure I apologize and not offend people that's all no, I don't think you're bending anybody you're fine
I'm gonna put away some of this food. I'm gonna leave the burger out, but I'm gonna put away
What the fries and the jalapenos so I'll have those later
Do you know what the chunk in the jalapeno the better the bite?
Really?
Okay, well this is the heaviest things in the bag so putting these in the fridge
Okay
It's like a quiet day. How was your day? Is it just a calm quiet day?
It's been like a normal day in the UK. How's it been in America for care for you?
America, it's a little overcast. I didn't sleep all day. Hi, baby. I slept all day and you know
Hey, baby
But, but we do have Donald Trump visiting Scotland at the moment and then coming to then going to
a steed visit, oh dear.
He is? Okay, so Trump is, yeah, so where has he been?
Um, yeah, he's Scotland. Yeah, is he golfing over there golf courses man to Embry
Aberdeen and the other one
There's a Trump national golf course. Hey, sweetie. There's a Trump national golf course that is
near
Or impals Verdes, it's right on the ocean. It's beautiful golf course, but it's like so that one's pretty much the near where I grew up
Which is like kind of said it's one of those beautiful places in the world really, but it's a golf course right on the right on the the cliffs
But all he said was too much immigration too much immigration and too many windmills
Committee windmills
Yeah
So anyway, yeah, I slept I slept all day. I had these crazy dreams
Well, some of them were like six scary
But I like to dream you like to dream
Me it have you ever heard of lucid dream? Yeah
That's where you're like conscious inside the dream, right? And you can control a dream
I've heard of lucid dreaming
Whoa
Have you done it
Who says I'm not part of your dream right now?
Why I believe that's you like life can be a dream like
Gently down the stream
Mary Mary Mary Mary life is about a dream
right
Whoa
Well anyway, all I've got to say about dreaming
You won't let me say what I've got to say about dreams.
Go ahead, say it, say it, say what you want to say.
What?
Your dreams are not our dreams, our dreams are not your dreams.
That is the problem with humanity.
There is no common humanity dream, that's why you're so divided.
Well we are all in a, we all are in a shared dream in a certain way, right?
We're all dreaming together, we can create this, we can get a dream or a nightmare.
The only dream you're living is a corporate dream, it.
Where you bow down to the dollar, you are a corporate fucking number,
and you need to be lived in a system of a corporate dream.
So, again, what I said was,
indefinitely corporality is dreams are either lucid or a corporate dream just
like the matrix well yeah like but I don't I don't get scared in my dreams I
like I have like
Some kind of the good control of that even though it was very scary. It was kind of like like I was saying there's a show called
Freddy's Nightmares. It was a nightmare on Elm Street
TV show
It was when I watch it when I was a kid. It was like most it was like so frightening
I could barely like move after you watch it and you can still watch it on YouTube. Look up Freddy's nightmare
I've never seen the show, but I've seen the movies. You know me. Yeah
The show is very different. The show is all like disjointed and it's just like it's just trippy
It's like it takes everything the show is like takes place in night in nightmares and stuff like that and so
And so they're just like very strange
Can't even describe it. Yeah, just check out a Freddy's nightmares on you can check it on on YouTube. I think it is on YouTube
It's all I can tell you know for a fact is what Disney's trying to do with Star Trek is very wrong
What are they trying to do the Star Trek?
Make it Gen Z
Well, it's gonna get worse and worse like that, you know, it's just like the whole world is
changing it's like the baby boomers are on their way out right it's like the and
so or there like there's there's many many of them so there's a huge
are on the way out but hardcore Star Trek fans including Star Wars fans
We don't give a fuck about them, we're just going to make everything re-fucking washed,
re-fucking produced and basically very friendly, no words will offend anybody and will affirm
anything you think of Gen Z. That's not Star Trek or Star Wars.
So we'll fuck them all these cunts at work at Disney in paramount and all those motherfuckers that cancel shit
Here we go, how are you guys doing you saw it on Amazon Prime recently, let's see. What'd you see on Amazon Prime?
British nightmares. Yes, it's on Amazon Prime
Thank you for letting me see that anyway. I mean it might fend a lot of people, but
Oh
Yeah, thanks everyone check out Sponkeys show tomorrow so Sponkey you got a congratulations
You got to if you're 15 subscribers, too, that's awesome. Just uh, you know have fun. I don't know if and you're just gonna talk to the camera
Whatever you do. I'm sure you'll
Charming and everyone will love you. So congratulations. Yeah, let's all let's all go support Sponkey tomorrow night. Maybe I'll try to
Oh
Are you another IRL circle yoga spunky? No, she's not she's she's friend, you know Gotti
She's friends with Gotti
Yes, I will come join I'll come join are you gonna do stream yard or are you gonna do just the live because
If you do it through stream art, you can put up comments on the screen stuff is it just fun
I wish I would have known about it started back up fucking me tesh. Hello. He touched your ballot
You need a wrench ASAP make it happen stream yard. Okay, you're gonna be streaming our perfect. Yeah, that'd be great show and
I mean when ESAP make it happen. Hi. I'm halo
Which channel is Freddie's nightmare? I think it was like on I just remember it was on like I think it's like channel 13 KCOP like
You know or there's something like that
it was like on on Saturday nights probably like 10 p.m. Or like maybe 11 p.m. and
and
It took I remember I heard about it like way before I ever saw an episode like it was it just like took forever
And then now it's on USA and stuff so
Are many you remember that show? That's it's a trippy show. I think but I think it's on it's on a YouTube now like
The they probably will have like the meant the network on it will play say it on it or something
You know on the little well, I quite a lot. I actually watch quite a lot stuff like that
But did you know that the X files are a series 10 and 11? Have you seen them yet?
X file series 10 and 11 now
They also made a Friday the 13th show, yeah, there was a Friday the 13th show.
But the Nightmare in Elm Street was cool because Freddie would make an appearance at the very beginning and the very end.
He would introduce it and close it out with a little sub-plot to the show.
And then the whole other show would be something unrelated where it would be usually like some guy in love with some girl.
She tries to unalive them and stuff.
The new Twilight Zone?
No, I haven't seen it but I want to see it. I love Twilight Zone.
Do you know what though?
I actually loved Halo of the series 1 and 2. I fucking thought it was fantastic. Master Sergeant.
Wow, but it's probably going to get cancelled. You know what I mean? It already has been.
Thank you fish taco stand. How does that sound? Yeah, let's go to the fish taco stand.
You saw the Friday 13th show when they used to work at the antique store. Oh, yeah, I remember that the kind of yeah
The new Twilight Zone I want to see I love the Twilight Zone episode called
It's about a doll and the dolls name is
Named is I forgot the doll's name, but oh it's like, but it's so so good the doll like the guy tries to like kill the doll and
The doll was like indestructible and would like it's talking. He's called talking Tina. Look up talking Tina
Yeah, he was pretty he was pre-banned tonight
Earlier time of the episode before
Yeah, hello, psycho wagons. Hello. Hello
I mean, sorry. Sorry. I thought that was your friend as in, you know,
Cyclean as in
Who was? Oh, who all these people are my friends in my channel. Do you have a favorite X-Files episode?
Oh, I really didn't watch too much X-Files. I did watch a few episodes and I did like it, but it was just like
You know, it's just like one of those shows I did not really watch
Well, you might want to watch series 10 and 11
It was the biggest piss-take, but also the biggest confirmation
Yeah, well, I don't watch really much TV anymore right now unsolved mysteries
Oh, yeah, I love like Robert Stack unsolved mystery. This is an unsolved mystery and it would be like there's a really good
I think one of the first episodes of it. It's about this girl
that like disappears out of thin air, like when she gets picked up by like a producer,
like a Hollywood producer just disappears out of thin air. I don't know if you ever remember
that episode I'm talking about but it's Hollywood producer, who it is? The director or producer
and she was like and she was like trying to get big and then she got to fight with her brother
or something and so he was like looking for years later but
And she was she's already going crazy though. She's are thinking maybe Luma Naughty was following her and like that
Telling story like if I disappear that this thing happened to me like blah blah this happened after she went to some strange party
Yeah, it's like the weirdest episode. Do you remember that one? You see the one base in your hometown at Cocoa Beach
No, I have to watch that. I think I have that on on prime. I have access to access to unsolved mysteries
So if you know the episode, let me know
It's that what you're talking about. I know there's this beautiful blonde chick and she was like and then she
She would just went missing like if she got picked up by somebody and she went missing from her house
Which she was like running away from home or leaving her house and yeah, I think it's an I think it's like the first
Episode of the season too. I don't remember exactly. Yeah, Tammy. Yeah
The guys you have to look up that story of Tammy because it's such an interesting story. She's like she saw it but
I love the group
Yeah, it's I think it's in unsolved mysteries. Okay
It was on unsolved mysteries is one of the that was a Robert Stack show where he would like being a trench-coated
This is unsolved mysteries, but as we watch I used to watch America's most wanted and there's another show
I wish like what's watch cops a lot back in the 80s. I love some of the original cops episodes those were great
and
unsolved mysteries and then
America's most wanted with you know John Walsh
Tammy Lynn Leppert so you can guys can look that's an unsolved mystery Tammy Lynn Leppert, right?
And it's a very interesting story. I can see if I can find anything about it on my tablet
tell you the
the rundown of it because
Just remember thinking that was like just one of the ones that took got my attention, you know
I was like, maybe she's like in Hollywood right now is like some under some other name or something like her
She became Katy Perry or something
Just like Katy Perry
Jeff Bezos Bell and and say look at my Daisy in space. Oh
Can you then leopard okay, what okay, so so here's what she looked like I have a picture of her
She's like a very beautiful woman right right. Tell me you like Katie Perry tea. I
Like some of her music. Yeah
She was missing in a mysterious circumstance is that she was born in Florida on February 5th, 1965 so Aquarius
She was participating in beauty contest when she was four years old just before
Disappearance she appeared in the film Scarface as the girl who distracts the lookout car during the bloody chainsaw scene
Before that among other minor roles. Yeah, she was in Scarface. Yeah
Yeah, it says after the spring break she was finished, Lepper went unaccompanied to a party
one weekend.
According to her close friend, Wing Flanagan, she came home under...
from the party a different person. After performing her role in Scarface,
Leppert suddenly returned home after the fourth day of filming. Her mother assumed that Leppert
had been afraid of being murdered by someone and had become overtaken by this delusion.
Her mother felt obliged to have her examined by a doctor, but after 72 hours in a medical center,
Leppert was released and there seemed to be no signs of drug or alcohol used during her,
according to doctor statements. She was last seen in Cocoa Beach, Florida on July 6, 1983.
worn a blue denim skirt that grew with flowers along with a matching skirt of gray person sandals.
Some agencies have stated that Leopard left without shoes or money. A male friend told authorities
that he had an argument with her while driving her from her home in Rockledge and had later left
her in a parking lot. Although he is the last person believed to have seen her, he is not considered
a suspect. However, Leopard's mother has claimed that her daughter was afraid of him. After her
Harold Lewis received two telephone calls from a woman claiming she was still alive in the first call
The woman said leopard would make contact when time was right during the second call
She said leopard was doing what she always wanted to do ghost to school and become a nurse
So that's weird
So let's let's boil it down. How do you feel about Katie Perry in Jeff Bezos's?
Fucking full of women
Ballant that went to space. How do you feel about all?
What's up, grossed?
Hey, good, bro. What?
Am I upset in you? How do you feel about Katie Perry?
I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't think about
I don't I don't have any opinion about it. Let's talk about all the girls that win
Hey ghosts, how are you?
Hi
mean I'm sorry I'm trying to concentrate with ghosts right now and
say you're talking about Jeff Bezos and Katy Perry and non-stop did you
anyway oh I missed that yeah you missed I heard that I didn't hear you're
talking to me right yeah yeah I heard a little bit of that but then I jumped on
and then uh yeah I was just listening to him my bad I was going off on Katy
Perry I didn't even hear Jeff Bezos but oh guess who's up here have you met
No porn bombing. Oh, I'm out of the other night. Oh, yeah, the other night. Yeah. Hey, what's up, dude?
Hey, what's up, bro?
How are you tonight?
I'm okay, bro. I'm okay, bro. You know what I got some to say bro. I got some fuck. I got some fucking
Crazy diamond shit fucking stalking me, bro. What the fuck is up? Who's talking you?
He said
Diamond diamond diamond is talking you what happened bro, bro. You have no idea, bro
What happened have you talked to the diamond on the phone, bro, I came here bro a couple times bro, and this bitch won't leave me alone
30 diamonds harassing you. Hi, spunky. I got 40 diamonds harass. Yeah, go ahead. Yeah, how's she harassing other and what's going on, man?
Did I say did I say she's harassing me? I didn't say she's harassing. You said she's stalking you. I'm just stalking. I'm pretty sure that's what he said, yeah
How she's thought I'm just asking
So she found she found she found where the fuck I hang
She went over there, bro. What the fuck bro?
Fuck's going on over here, bro
Yeah, I show up over here I show up over here and what what happens what happened
No, like the unsolved mysteries. Was that the same girl? Oh, yeah, that is the same girl. Yeah, the Tammy Lynn Tammy Lynn
Yes, I remember watching that weird isn't it that it's like yeah talking about you. Yeah. Yeah, crazy
It was recently. Yeah, it was and it was one of those like, you know urban legends like obviously you did disappear
But like everybody was always like be careful. No, well playing, you know, you're you're a single girl
You'll get
So yeah, and she was in Scarface too. I didn't I forgot about that part where she was in Scarface. Yeah
Before I grew up there, but
She was in Scarface, she like leaned into the car or something
She's like distracted somebody when in the chain. There's a chainsaw scene and yeah tracks like the getaway car or something
And oh, was she in a was she in a was she in a bikini or no? Yes. She was I think it was gold. Okay. I know I know
Yeah, I know
Beautiful girl beautiful girl
But she like it's weird because she kind of lost her mind and then went to the mental hospital for a little bit
And then and then disappeared so nobody really knows if she went like apeshit crazy and like just off herself and
To who knows where or she really was kidnapped, but she had paranoia about after she went to Hollywood about they'll be like
It was never specified as the Illuminati, but like people were coming to get her and stuff
So I don't believe it with enough paranoia though
You can't snap though and like because there's a case and I'm sure you seen the video of the dude
Where the last video of him was in the airport where he just took off sprinting out of the airport for no absolute no reason
You know history over nothing, but they said he had what happened was before that he did get beat up
I guess and but anyways, he was a head paranoia and I I don't
Nobody knows what really happened, but he snapped. Well, that's what they think happened. I just like it was
Three diamonds here guys your boyfriends here. Yeah diamond. Don't don't don't stop anyone. Okay
Diamond. He said you're stalking him. Are you?
Diamond what's going on? I can't have people stalking people from my show. Okay, I'll get under control. Okay?
I'm gonna talk to her. I'm gonna tell her get off ringer up sparky
We're gonna sort this out diamonds. I'm gonna sort this out
Follow my friend auto around please. Yeah auto. You're not interested
I don't know
Psych yeah
You like diamond or no?
I'm busy during the day. I'm free after 4 o'clock PM. Oh, okay. Oh
You're up for for harassment
Are you don't psyched on diamond?
It's okay. I just I just I just had no idea that she will go to this other fucking channel where I'm at
but sir, it's you know what it is. It's the beard. It's working
It's cute auto. I'm digging it. I was thinking I was thinking at the other night. Oh, I wasn't thinking it's cute
But I'm saying it's working
Yeah, look at it. Auto. Oh
Man
Oh
Can I ask what diamond did when she when she went over there? Oh, sorry when she went over this
I'm so sorry when she went over there. Um, what did she do?
Yeah, Otto you're looking for
Okay, let me know when you're available Otto
What's up? Hey?
What do I see here?
Why did you stalk me, Otto?
Oh, god, that's a jump scare.
Now you stalked me, Otto.
That's not a jump scare.
Be nice to her.
Otto, are you stalking Danny, too?
Yeah, Otto's a good guy.
Be nice.
It was just really wrong.
I was on Gacy's channel earlier.
It's like, he was on Jaycees and Otto.
He said that he was going to pay for me.
Otto also dance for me without a shirt. He then started a chair for me and he also asked to
See oh my god and everything. Yeah, he also asked me to whip it out. Oh my god
Let this man finish this conversation. You might have to be able to defend himself a lot
He's been leading you on a lot happened on jason's panel. Just oh Jesus
Yeah, I was on Jaycee's channel because I saw Otto on there, one of the fucking Adam and yeah, Otto was like, I'm going to, I told Otto I'm not going to let him fucking trace what Otto said.
Okay, well you sell out, so I'm going to buy it then.
Alright, I'll back up, I'll be quiet.
What's going on?
Otto, honey, you like my smile?
Otto?
I do flirty.
Thank you, punchy.
By the way, Diamond does I don't know I don't want to be rude and I don't want to ask
I don't ask to see my dick in balls. He's anyone else. Okay. Well, that's all. All right. I'll mute. That's all I wanted to know.
Yeah, I had to look it from the back.
Ghost? Oh my god, right?
Otto, it's the car. It's the car.
Slurred
And he was bullhunching a chair what you didn't say well now, sorry I made that up, but he was
Explained to his friends
You know what you know, it's like you when I get scared I get stuck you know what I usually do
First thing check your number. Hi. Hi. Yeah. No start hopping a chair third thing, you know start dancing around for thing
I'm about I was I was talking to somebody over here. Oh, why are you why are you bothering the homeless people for?
We the homeless people alone
I don't know how many of you
got you got you got you got you
got you got you got you got
you got you got you got you
you got you got you got
Gotta hey bro, I get all kinds of people come to me for things. It's okay. Nobody goes up to for anything auto
You don't have any hair your body
Are you guys are you guys making a joke out of this or this really happened?
Did this actually happen? No, this actually happened. This happened on J.C.
It happened on J.C. Lacey's
I don't literally I told Otto I wouldn't let him fucking me for free and Otto's like, okay
Well, you saw ass. I'm just gonna pay for it then and then after that I told I told Otto to dress
To dance shirtless for me. So Otto started dancing shirtless for me
He then
You're smiling into the fucking camera dude
Wait, wait, Otto, can we see the shirt?
I thought you could stop
Otto, can you show them the shirt?
Let's dance, can you do this for me?
Can you show them the shirt?
Can I see it, Otto?
Somebody else coming in
Are you gonna dance?
Play a dance
I don't know why you're dancing to that.
So what's the move, Otto?
Just lift up your shirt.
Come on, Otto. Let's see it.
No? OK.
What's the run under there, Otto?
Go through.
So, do it.
I don't want to say the full screen auto dance for us again. Can you dance for me again without a shirt?
Come on. Come on auto auto. Can you take your shirt off for me?
He's a little bit you guys done
No, I don't wear underwear psyche. He doesn't wear underwear. You don't wear underwear. No, he walks around
Don't take off your pants
Know everything. I thought you were here. You send yourself first. You've made the claim that diamonds talk to you
Then you made the claim well the first depth
I think that was the only claim you actually made and then you made it sound like
But hey diamonds here. Hey, does it sound like that's the case at all brother? Yeah
Him and I got divorced a couple hours ago.
I divorced him a couple hours ago.
I sold the ring.
Come on, if I make as you should.
As you should.
But how did you end up in a JC Wasey's panel together?
Like, how'd you find each other there?
Well, I know about JC because of Rageen.
So like, I was growing through people that I'm following,
and I saw Otto on there.
So I said, I put him high.
Oh.
and so with a lot of panels I just type in like open panel and then I just put
whose lives and then I should not look I was never there though by the way hey I'm
not taking a claim on this argument at all I was never there right so yeah yeah
yeah yeah who is the lady beside you it's funky funky the blood
Her above you. Yeah, yeah, that's funky. Yeah. Yeah, who's that's funky? That's funky my friend spunky
Great, you know what it is. Are you gonna dance for us? I mean if you want me to
Oh, yeah. Okay. Go ahead.
Mike, would you like him to dance like you?
Yeah. You're loud.
Dance for us. One auto, show us a move.
Can you show me exactly how you did it for Diamond
after you claimed that she's talking?
Can you show me exactly how you danced?
Yeah, he needs to take off his shirt.
He needs to take off his shirt and lower his pants.
He had his pants all the way to where it was.
No, we're not going to lower it.
To where the outline was.
Yeah.
His pants are down all the way to the very outline.
Just take off your shirt.
All you do is just take your shirt.
I will call her Diamond.
I call her crazy demon.
OK, crazy demon.
You like her, though, huh?
You like her?
Right there, right there.
You like this one?
Auto, that's nice.
Yeah, you like her.
I like this one.
I like a smile auto auto your name's auto auto your name's auto cuz you like transformers Broom Broom
You want a diamond to join the panel and he actually wanted to have the diamond that was the whole point
I think he likes time here
I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I don't have it. I
No, I don't know how many more of these songs are good.
No.
Spunkies, spunkies, like a natural born woman.
Spunkies, all women.
They're gender women, they swear.
Spunky only has one, there's only one thing fake about Spunky.
My titties.
And it's her titties.
Let me see you.
Let me see you turn on your cam. First of all
You
Yeah
Take your shirt off and dance
You know, I'm not a bitch. I'm a man. I don't you dance for me when I
We're just trying to appreciate the beauty here. I'll leave the room. So you have some
Otto's um, thank you will put on his beetle for you and dance for you
First of all, I'm a man first of all
so
You don't fucking you don't throw dollars at me to dance
You understand nobody offered you money. Nobody offered you money. Not you auto. You just started dancing for me for free
You told me you wanted to pay to fuck me and they started stripping for me
Where do you get so much stories so many stories from there
This literally happened on jaycee waysees. Fuck you me
Yeah, I dance. Yeah, of course I dance. I like to dance. Did you dance for diamond? Yes or no, that's the claim
Did you dance for diamond? I literally told you to dance for me, and you did.
Well then what the hell? You have no fucking argument here. I was trying to have your back, but yeah, you done bet it. You did it, brother.
See? People don't know.
The way your diamond doesn't lie about these type of things. I've done enough proof on so many different things.
I
I think you're treating this like a stick, but I you guys look like an actual couple like if you if I was like in
In Miami or fucking Naples, Florida. That's not good. Doesn't it like I would literally think you guys were a couple
So I don't know why you think this is a joke like you guys should be funny. I'm
I mean you're acting like it's a joke though. I'm taking
Crazy demon. I want everybody to know that I love your smile. I love your smile. Oh
My mother are oh, you guys are having babies soon. I can see
Hey, I know I know that thing has testicles and a sausage. I know that I know whoa, whoa, whoa, 30 diamonds the dick
I didn't know I had a dick the whole time, but I like your smile, but I don't love you.
I'm sorry.
Ghost, is that real?
No, that's fucking crazy.
Um, what?
What is what, girl?
Sorry, man, that's being there.
I'm sorry, dude.
Oh my what is diamond rule? I mean
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry to get in the middle of your love story that was
I don't want to fucking tell me to dance, and I'm gonna fucking start dancing like a monkey
Shut the fuck up you filthy whore
Like it I like it I mean
God, this is not why I thought it was going a different way.
I guess I know. No, he's my son. I thought this is going to hold it for a while. He's my son.
I didn't believe Diamond. I didn't believe it, but yeah.
It's going the right way. It's going the right way. My dick ain't going in no vagina at all, sir.
Would you like to explain that again?
Excuse me, my dick goes into a vagina only.
Diamond, you gonna take that for him?
I don't know if he said he was gonna pay to fuck me
unless Aldo wants to switch to a dick that gets fucked in the ass.
And the dick's gonna go into...
Can I say that word?
The dick's gonna go into the what Aldo?
I want to talk to that girl right about me.
Nah, it's monkey's.
Huh?
Yeah, I'll talk to you
Got you gotta dance. I want you I want you to come on camp first and then I'll dance
Not dance for a hunter if you got it. Oh, if you got a hundred bucks, I'll do it
I'm sure I came on dance right brother. I
Want I want this woman shirt on those shirt on
Kim Kim
My boy is just enjoying
We don't want shirts off listen
He's not the general he likes it
Don't show me a little picture like that. Show me yourself came up come up right about me right about me come up
Okay, I'll come up. I'll do it right now. I have a mustache and I'm smoking a sugar. I'll came up right now
You're not gonna put me full screen in there I want okay
So joke so joke you're supposed to put the bald man on there cuz I don't know what
You will never okay. You will never come up T. Y. You stupid. Oh shit jump scare
You will never come up T. Y. You stupid
Bitch you see my face literally what was that last night?
Anyways, ain't no girl about me. Hey listen, sir. You're never gonna make it. Hey listen Otto for real on some real shit
Hey, no, no, no, let's talk. Let's talk on some real shit. You're never gonna. You're never gonna debate me
You're never gonna fucking out talk me after what after what diamond said you just admit all this shit
You could never talk about that
You know that right I gave you every benefit of the doubt. I just fucking try to defend you
I even want to debate it with you
But Diamond at this point Diamond didn't even say anything incorrect
You said something incorrect. I think you said that he was uh, she sorry
She was talking you and you no burden of proof about that
But then Diamond came here and claimed all this shit about you dancing to all this shit and you went
Yeah, that's right
So, you're never going to be able to talk to a person like me. You understand that, right, Otto?
We're not the same level. You understand that.
We're not the same level. We're not the same level. You understand that.
That's my job.
You're not the same level. You understand that.
You're not the same level.
Can you talk can you stop talking to me? I'm talking to this girl right here
Which girl are you talking to?
You're pointing at me dumb fuck
Come up. You're never gonna talk to her. You understand that, right? You're never gonna talk to her, so you understand that, right?
Right now, and I will dance
After what that you agree to it after I you had an argument was like I thought diamond was actually stalking your ass
I thought we had actually I was like, oh shit. Yeah diamond bad bad bad guy. That's what he said
That's what he said in the beginning. That's what he said
Why would you be a fucking liar for your lying ass fucking whore?
You're lying ass whore.
Bitch, I've never been stalking your fucking old and you have a fucking bald spot.
You have a bald spot right here.
I'm tractable, you don't count, okay?
You don't count.
How am I aligning for?
I'm not aligning for.
I could say a couple of choose choice words where I'm not going to do that.
I'm 23 year old is going to stalk your 50 year old ass.
Like, I would never stalk you.
Like, you have to pay to be my fucking presence auto.
You have to pay to be my presence, you know?
Wait, diamond real quick.
Can you ask him why he said that he stalked him?
I told you to go on Staky's panel with him to do auto.
You were a good little boy and you listened to me and you went on fucking Staky.
Oh, shit.
When I told you to
You just got diamond on you
You said you were gonna suck my dick from the fucking back.
You said you were going to sell my dick in a fucking bag, Otto, you're a fucking dick, you're a fucking dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick, you're a dick,
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Spunky look what you did Spunky came up
Did you just say spunky?
You see that spunky?
I see my work.
What are you gonna show us your apartment you keep getting out outside?
Yo you wrinkle bro
Are you sure I know they've got out out there you know, he's been hanging out outside there for like the last two hours
He's been hanging out outside
Maybe that's where he lives sure
Although do not have an apartment like do not have like a home
Are you homeless actually doing these are go fund me?
We show we didn't you just say you just say you showed him your ball. So you showed a homestay your ball
No, he asked to see my balls, but he didn't give me money, so I didn't show my balls. Oh
God, oh
Yeah, you know, yes, I'm shitty gel
Wait, are we showing tattoos
I love that.
Yeah.
They're going to skeleton.
Please, Bunky. No gang signs.
No gang signs?
Oh, wait.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
about Otto, uh, asking to see his, her, whatever the fuck, diamonds, balls, you hear all that
about me?
And I'm not even trying to be rude tonight, I'm not even trying to crash up tonight,
you know, Jared?
Yeah, I'm gonna see your fucking balls diamond and I want to see your fucking dick
and that's why you gotta be careful you fucking you think I try to descend out of
and I thought I got up here and everything I need that I need that I need money
if he wants to see my balls and dick and auto
and that's what I really need
Don't worry. I am gonna go that way. How much the how much the pay the national
A little press you want to give that? Yeah, I want to get funky
You literally have six inches auto like you can't
I already seen his dick everybody's seen it. God damn auto. Wow
Oh god, now you saw it never mind
His old wrinkle butt yo
Like it's your birthday, go auto, it's your birthday.
We're gonna smoke a pot, like it's your birthday, you heard?
Oh my God.
Yo, he's funny.
He's dancing.
Hey, he is getting down a little bit.
What the fuck?
I don't want to see that shit.
Yeah, that's all for you diamond
I don't want that shit
Is it a for psyche?
Bunky yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, he did it for spunky
Now you're taking my man spunky. No girl. No, never
We're going to fight. We're going to fight. We're going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I'm going to fight. I
You want to know who I know?
I know myself.
That's it? You don't know Joseph?
I know my son.
I know nobody.
I don't know anybody.
I'm sorry. He said he knew you.
I just wanted to say hi from him.
No, I don't know about I know myself. I know myself
Well, do you know yourself because you're you're going that spunky and you're gonna diamond that's way different brother
I'm not even to get on like I'm like why I'm not even to get on all that
Like sex
What else is different without poor bonds, you know what else is different. This is different
This is different. Please don't show anything dude. Come on. Oh my god. Is he in a porn bomb? Oh, no, he's blunching again
I was so scared there
Oh my god.
That's different. That's different. That's different.
Hey, Elias, that boy just hit the arm. Different. Yeah, I'm different.
Ha ha, you heard it. Oh my god.
You know
Fuckers hot coping all he does is cope. Hey, do you want can I be how serious gonna get with it?
Cuz you're gonna get like we're going against like right whatever
But I could you said that the other night, but I can see you hurt all I want
What's your problem with it? If you want to debate about it? Let's fucking run it
You're gonna sit there. You're gonna shut the fuck up and they're gonna tell me what to do because you know better
I will school you right now. You don't know if you want a dick or a pussy dumb dumb
Yard you really want to break it down? I can say whatever I want. At least I know what the fuck I want, Yard.
Straight up, Yard.
Yard. You didn't hear. You didn't hear basic fucking. You didn't hear basic. Like you don't know the difference between sex.
At all. What do you want, Yard? You were bullhunching for diamonds. You looked at her dick, and then you bullhunched for spunky.
What do you want, brother? Can I ask? What do you want?
You don't have to say that stupid. I don't have to say it, but I'm gonna say I'm gonna be glad when I say I'm gonna smile when I say
you heard. Oh, I forgot to mention Otto also having moaned his name earlier. He was having me moaned his name earlier.
Otto, you're a fucking idiot. Otto, you're a worst-in-diamond and I'm making the burden of proof beyond me. I'll go ahead and make that claim, you're...
And now you know what I'm gonna say every time I talk to you out of them to say you're heard at the end of it
You're
Yeah, you're gonna do shit about it. So what's your argument? Are you gonna slide inside? So say you're heard anymore?
You're gonna bitch slap me but you're the bitch that falls for a bitch that is actually a male but pretends to be a bitch you're heard
I'm trying to crash the fuck out tonight yours
Keep it up. I'll give you one more chance. I'll crash the fuck out. Keep it up yours
Yeah, shut there and shut up boy
Like the little bitch well kind of a fake
You're kind of confused. You don't know what you want. We don't even know if you're
Never crash out. I'm not gonna do night either because I only you know why cuz Ali s told me not to that's the only reason why
Sloppy silly sloppy silly bitch. Oh, no
I'm gonna slap me silly. I'm gonna slap you. I'll slap you at least you'll pick one after I slap you you heard
Well, maybe not but you're still gonna get fucking bitch slap your
Fucking annoying ass. I'm literally tired of saying you heard but you shouldn't even mention it. You're not gonna
Yeah
How am I stupid you don't know what the fuck you're talking about you can't but let us let me remind you how this fucking started
You came up here saying that diamond of all people diamond of all people was stalking you come to find out
He didn't uh, she didn't stalker. Sorry
Whatever it is. They didn't stalk you
It was actually you being aware though you're bullhunting this shit like she served you up
You're funky you're kind of a weirdo brother
You're not gonna go to spunky now dumb fuck. That wasn't all right never mind
You never had a fucking animal on top of you spunky
The same with Justin Boyle
Oh my god, like Otto is a funny character, like I've been trolling him this like for
the last two hours I've been trolling him and like he generally thinks that I want to
fuck.
Well my bad, I ruined that free time and my bad, I shouldn't even have joined, I wouldn't have had the likes and dislikes on a trolling, if I know they're trolling then yeah, I'll take it more further, but it's not bad.
I've been laughing this whole time, like earlier he was telling me how he wanted me to fucking slap his face with my dick.
Oh my god, Ellie, that's the picture.
No, he was drooling, his mouth was drooling.
Jesus, age Christ, look at that picture.
That's my boy. Oh, yes. Yeah, he he's no longer with us, right? He was a brave slow. Yeah. I'm still here. I'll come
Yeah, that picture's fucked up, buddy. I know I just found that online
Sorry, I didn't mean to laugh.
Nah, I found that online and I had to put it on.
Can we get a moment of silence in our piece for my boy Elias?
Yes, everyone shut the fuck up for a moment of silence.
For my boy Elias.
And now after our moment of silence, can I get you heard in the chat please?
For my boy.
He lives a good one though. He lived a real one. He was really really good. He did. He's a real one. Oh
My god, he was just so unhappy, you know, he was just always negative
I'd like to give him a few words.
Not unhappy.
He was stern. No bullshit.
That's okay.
Stern, you know?
Who was?
Hulk Hogan.
Did you not see him in the casket, Flirty?
Wasn't that the dude that said the hard R?
Yes, it was one time. He said that yes
Because his daughter was dating somebody yeah, he was like I don't care if he dates a black guy as long as he's a rich n-word I
Mean I read I mean that that's logical
Yeah, and you know it's funny actually met his daughter she's a very nice girl
But you know whatever I
Mean RIP, but at the same time of the dude was a racist and I don't really I
Know well at least you know
At least the dude was a dude
I'll say a whole coke your racist
Yeah
All them old white men are sadly, you know, it's not it's not excuse. It's just that they are
You're old you white you're racist
Depends on the person only when you're old and white
It's a lot of races everybody like any white person can definitely be racist
But now this dude has said a couple out-of-pocket things before like I don't know much about him
Besides that because like I don't watch sports. They bore me. So
You just have a retarded fucking thing. I'm not even right. Yeah
Yeah, white people are typically the most
If Barack Obama couldn't be racist if he didn't hire a white person.
I will tell you that racism is a choice because I had the top.
If Barack Obama didn't want to hire a white worker at all, is that not racist?
No, it's not.
You're fucking not only are you yeah, I you know what I expect after me diamond never mind
People that are literally like of color
If I went to Africa then and they refused to hire me just based on the fact that I'm white it wouldn't be racist
We shouldn't go to Africa then
I mean not only
Man
Black people to go to Africa all the time and I'll hear you are thinking you as a white man is gonna go to Africa and not have a
So white people cannot be racist at all is that your claim you can't be racist
Yeah, like it's it's hard for you guys. Can you be well, okay diamond here? All right. I'll give you the branch
Literally, there's a bill size you mean you guys
That isn't why can you be prejudiced like there's a whole bill
You know what the crown act is the crown act, you know, are you talking about the braids?
Hey, guess who had the braids? It was the fucking Vikings
You guys didn't have braids. Those weren't braids. Those were not box braids
Those were literally not those weren't braids. Those were not the fucking girl braids
Hey, listen, sir, you know, you're not I'm trying to respect like you see an old and he said I can't argue if he retards anymore
But I'm trying my hardest if there's a huge difference between the two trying my hardest
Corn rules are actually made to they created a map using corn rolls
They made a map so they can escape slavery. You guys. There's no
You can't be racist towards a white person is everybody gonna skip over that know what you're gonna realize that he just said that
The braves have Vikings worn there's no meaning
or even being in that nature. In fact, it was more like a dreadlock.
And you also even went a step further. You said you couldn't be prejudiced toward the white person.
You realized you just said that, right? Those were dreadlocks. Vikings had dreadlocks. They didn't
have... So if I went to Japan and I tried to work and they wouldn't hire me just on the basis that
Don't go somewhere that you guys have told black people to go to for such would that be answer my fucking question
Would that be prejudice or not?
Don't go somewhere. Don't look at me like I'm fucking retarded answer the question
Answer the question
The fact is why people have told black people is it racist?
Why are you here diamond just like cuz you like I don't why are you here? I'm kind of confused. I
Do wherever I go wherever I want
Okay, cool. You could find yourself somewhere else. Do you know you realize that right?
Can I get free speech? I mean, you're more than a psycho.
If you have to talk to a psycho, it's a psycho.
If a psycho wanted you to go on, he'd tell me.
But it's free speech. Listen.
You're a filthy
filthy fucking mouth. I mean
Yeah, don't click your fucking phone unless you want to rage but answer my fucking question. I'm not gonna let you escape the shit
Sponky answered for you, but you were not
Should I even ask that's not even worth asking a second question, you know, I'll let it go
racist or prejudice because at the end of the day white people have told black people to go to
uh-huh i'm talking about you do you hear the japan
story i don't honestly i don't want to go there all the time when you white people tell black people
to go there all the time when you do this bitch is racist well this dude is racist my dad my
father's telling me at 13 years of age he sat me down at the kitchen table and said
If you ever come home with a woman that you're dating or a black man, you were out of the family
What did I do? The first thing I did was find me a girlfriend. Got a black man. Oh my bad. No, sorry
Now smokey was your was your old man, right? Hey, some was your old, uh, hi, baby
Um, I'm sorry. Did you want to go? Sorry? Go ahead, Summer.
He was the most racist.
No, go ahead, Gus. I didn't mean to interrupt you. Go ahead.
Yeah, I was going to ask.
Nah, yeah, I was going to ask, that's fine, because you were actually...
I'm not even trying to get it with the iron make it's not worth it. He was a giant asshole. He was a giant asshole
yeah, I believe it everybody and
and sexist and
You know like homophobic and I just you know, yeah, oh shit. Yeah
Blew all of those stereotypes out of the water became myself
So, you know, you can become a free thinker. It doesn't matter what your parents think you could you can do big
Whatever you want to be, wherever you want to be, wherever you want to be, where you want to come from.
Somewhere do you hear what diamonds said earlier with auto? Well, I just um, so I came up I came up to say something so actually
People of color can be prejudiced, right?
The only reason the difference between racist and prejudice is a power structure, right?
And since here in America, they didn't have that they don't have that certain power structure
They definitely can be priced prejudice. So which means the same thing pretty much in racist
So don't ever think that somebody of color cannot be like, you know
hateful because of somebody's skin color it's just that it's the bias and the and the racism
It's just the power structures only thing it makes it different
But it's the same shit and when I make the example about Japan obviously if you go to Japan Japan people are in power
So obviously they can be racist towards white people. It's just like it's it's not America. It's not white people in power
like
You understand that right? Well, yeah, you use the example of Africa
But see the difference there is you're you're using something that was so this only stands here in America, right?
Because here in America black black people were a slave, you know big-time slaves and all that kind of shit, right?
But like over in Africa, you know, the power structure might be different
So it may not you know, they could it may be the racist stuff is over. I don't know
I don't know the ways of Africa or I just know the ways of America
I agree with you Summer, I agree with you Summer, I 100% agree, but also in the history.
especially of mankind like
Like if you break it down enough like there's been a lot of people that's been in sleep. I mean so
It's not by any way, I'm not here saying that only black people were slaves
Well, I can tell you I get to I can tell you right now black people own slaves and I can tell you that there were
And into the slaves there were our slaves. There were all kinds of different places especially here in America
I was taking it further than summer. I was going even further back in history. I know we're just talking about USA
Maybe that was my mistake
Take on let me just say something for a second. It's hurt. You better stay off my man
What the hell's going on here?
What's up sexy beautiful lady, how you doing mama?
Of course, I'm talking to Spunky. I mean, David, hello. How are you, too beautiful, but wait for it? Oh, there's
I haven't seen her in a couple days, so I just want to say hi, sexy. How you feel gorgeous
Yeah, it's not yeah, I get it. It's all gravy. I figured you know
We're okay. Thank you. Why would you smile when I said that? I'm glad because I would hate you too
Come on. I love you both and I love spunky. She's amazing and got great tips. So we can I press her off
Can I oh, well, how do we know how would we know that?
Showed our boobs
I mean the burden of proof. Yeah, I mean you said she had
Hold on. Wait a minute. Hold on. Hold on. What's taking? What's taking? Hold on. Here it goes. Do you want it ghost?
You wanted to talk to my husband. I'm looking. Hey, there's nothing wrong with women sitting on a panel together shaking their tits at each other, is there?
Nope. All right. Thank you. Well, do you really want to do that?
Hold on wait a minute. All right. He said something. He just said something. What'd you say if the gas could shake the dingling?
And if the gas could shake the dinglings, they could make a dingling. That's what he's saying holler
And shake my tits to other women right baby shake his dingling
Oh
Beautiful kids. Here. How about me? Here? Guess who's holding my phone right now? I just want to make sure I'm covered. I want to guess your husband.
My husband's holding my phone! Hello! Thank you. Just for the fucking record, mother fucker. My husband knows what I do on here. Just so you all know.
And yes, if my husband went to town, he could. I would care. It's a beautiful day.
Yes, I agree with you. It might be beautiful whatever, but would he like to run it? I know he doesn't he seems
I was just proving to you that my husband knows what I do online because
I never made that I know your husband knows that I know that
Okay, I just wanted to make sure because you did say that with the other night. No. Yeah. Yeah, I did make that guess
Yes, I did
Yeah, so all of our men know what the fuck we're doing. We're not up here just doing whatever
Well, why not
He wants a little piece. I'm glad to pay for it. We can we can run out take you your husband and her husband's funky
So then we can just have like a little three-way a little we didn't have to debate. We just like
A what?
What?
Well, I can explain it again.
Okay.
I could pay on psyche.
She and I could pay money on that summer's husband and a spunky boyfriend, husband, whatever
it is.
My husband would never.
We could have a little.
My husband doesn't know you.
We could have a little chat about it.
No
Would never get on panels and debate anybody he just won't
It's about his thing. Well, that's just sir. Maybe he needs to listen not even like participate. Maybe he just needs to listen
He don't need to listen to shit. This is my fun time. This is I mean like what's the big deal?
Yeah, he's here everything. We live in the same fucking house when i'm telling you guys
I'm gonna binge you over and peg you motherfuckers. You think my husband don't hear me screaming that of course he does
right
Attractibles know me for a long time
I'm like, how many times we're
gonna get it? I've known you for
a while. I know and you should
know that. So you should know
that my husband always hears
everything. Yeah. Yeah. That's
the problem though. That's the
issue. That's the issue that I
have. I don't want to argue with
people. That's the issue that I
had. That's why I offered a little
I would even pay for it, but I don't want to get into it
But why are you worried about another man this race 10 children has four grandbabies
Oh, it's his own property. Take care of his wife. How are you gonna tell another man?
What are you gonna do with his old lady if I smoked Matt? Should I tell you should I be able to tell you that it's not okay to smoke that?
Yes
Now listen
You try to throw it because actually summer because it was actually like a big thing deal like a couple nights or whatever
That I did want to talk to your husband
And then what you want to throw that shit in there a little bit until like you got a jab in there because I will fucking pay money
And we can all run it. We can even talk about it. I don't even want to we do off-air. We know
I
Showed my tits how about that like how better can you get yeah? I would love to talk about it. Yeah
He talked to you about what he does not care about his wife doing so then why the fuck would you make a punch like
About what you let or not let your wife do who like what the fuck
If you want to fight with him
He's in the chat Justin Boyle down there. You want to tell him what's up fight with him
No, I've heard about Justin boy. I don't know who the fuck it is, but we out weren't with him
Where we have
Summer here's the real quick though. Love you summer by the way
You're not gonna throw in a like a because you see how that was kind of like a little bit like fucked up
Like you threw in like a little jab there and you're like hey, let me you can talk to my
Know your husband's there I know you're
But I ask for a call
I
I'm just saying I will never understand that's kind of weird. I'm just saying I don't want to have an argument about it
It's kind of weird that you threw that in there somewhere
You did that to like try to prove a point. You didn't prove nothing, but that's all right
I'm not I definitely proved a point that my husband knows what I'm doing hollers
White nights he was talking. He's like I would have talked to your husband. I was like
Yes, I do why not how many times I gotta repeat fuck it. Let's run
If he wants to run it, we can run it
We're in the same room. What do you want to talk to him about?
He's a fucking white knight simp anybody to let their
Go in the chat he wants to talk to you
Here's your fucking one of a million chance. Go ahead. Yes. Hello
Hello, yeah speak
You're throwing this on me. I think my argument was that you're I'm pretty sure this is what it was that you're a white night
Simp and you let your because I think I has only fans and everything
I'm pretty sure I know you're throwing this on me all once, but you fuck it. We can run it
Yes, you know, I'm sure you're right
Have you subscribed to it nice to the YouTube one up?
Because I'm not I don't I'm not a white night. So I don't why would I
I want to just take a moment to say you have an amazing wife and thank you for allowing her on the internet or whatever happens
And that's called you know what that's called
You don't like titties
Do you feel well? Let me ask you a quad you don't ask me all these stupid
Let me ask you a question. Do you feel proud that your your woman shows tits pussy and ass on the internet for everyone to see
Yeah, I love her
You you you feel proud about that
It is what I guess I didn't ask you if you loved your ass if you felt proud about that
Cuz I love you sir. You're sure you're sharing it with ha you're sharing it with hundreds of people you love it
You can have this let us assume that you can have the same woman let us assume look I'm talking no
Let's run this bitch. Let us assume you can have the same. All right. That's fair
What?
All right, I'll go ahead let us assume you get up the same woman, but imagine she didn't share her body online
She wasn't that broken anything like that
You could you push the button to get summer when she's only fans
What am I gonna say that word but only fans?
Shares the body with everyone or you push the button when
Fuck it summer and she's virgin. What button are you gonna push?
I mean, I mean, that's just like asking our could we assume that you
Never had any pussy before and that
What's button are you gonna push?
What do you know when you
Everybody see you everybody what button are you gonna push answer the question are you gonna let them answer?
Do you know when you walk outside everybody she's everybody looks
Yeah, but nobody
Have the issue of people looking at you
Yes, sir, but then nobody sees their tits and pussy sir
Marriage where you can like, you know, cuz like it's what you know, that's like he'd like him answer the question
Let's run that bitch dog. Let's let's run it
What button would you push?
Fantasy realm the worthy vision envision it in a button. Would you push answer my question?
I mean, are you scared of your body to where you got a question somebody else's?
Answer my fucking answer the question. Don't ask one. You can ask after right after you answer it. You can ask it
Click the virgin button. What what is it? What?
All right, let's assume let's assume that you're dating. I don't even know how I'm talking at this point, but you're dating summer, right? Correct
I'm married. Yes. Yes
We're married married to summer. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah married to someone
Let us assume that you could push a button
You get summer only fans
Whatever you want to call it busting open for anyone ask titties assholes all out there for anyone to see
You know kids and everything or you could push a button. He is
You're gonna listen sir, you're gonna be the same summer. She's gonna be a virgin. That's gonna be the same one
Which one you pick?
I'd want the one I got now because that's the fun one
That's the happy one. Yeah, but it's the thing though. It will be the same thing. It's just she never done any of that
No, it's not
No, it is
And spunky right now are not the same people
So you're not going to answer the question though.
You're going to run away from it.
That's fair.
Honestly bro, if I was you, I'd run to you.
I'd run to you.
I want the sixth one.
We're 18 years
Babe, I wish you would not wasn't a whore or I wish you didn't sell pigs or what you're not gonna tell her that
If you ask Justin right now if you would rather have
Smoky, you don't have to make it about yourself to you I was talking I was talking about
Yeah, I was talking about
You're just saying
I was talking to them
Yeah, but I'm glad she's not a virgin
Does that answer questions not a virgin so is that summer's husband speaking is that summer's husband?
Mr. Summer, Mr. Summer, how did you feel when she when she wore that shirt saying
Which one
The one who I love Peggy man like big dick
I love I love Peggy man. How did you feel about that? Yeah, go ahead. Yeah, I picked that one. How'd you feel?
There's nothing wrong with the truth
And he bought the search for
That's why you never fucking debate me this why I can never pay enough money to fucking debate them
That's all I wanted to know about this woman. I the first time I saw her
Saying I love pegging men that's that's all I wanted enough
Ooh, who said that?
I won't tell you, Raindos.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I've never pegged a man in my life.
But there's nothing wrong with it, man.
You sure wore a shirt saying something.
They're going to pay some money.
That's not true.
They're going to pay some money here.
You want to get pegged?
There's some content you want to get paid. I'll pay you with two people who want to do that in a
Concentral relationship. There's nothing wrong with that and if you buckers have a problem with that you don't need to go
Get fucked yourself honestly
Answer the problem
I think it is a problem with that
Hold on one second. Can I answer I was in a rock concert at video at video FaceTime my husband
I showed him the shirt because it's my favorite saying he said you want the shirt. I said I do baby
I'll buy it for you. So what's the issue with the shirt?
It was great. It's a great shirt. Yeah, but you was out there wearing that shirt in front of little kids.
What the fuck was that? So are you. More logical than that. What the fuck was the point of that?
You was out there wearing that shirt in front of little kids, so...
I was at a metal concert. I wore the shirt wherever I was, sir. I'm a grown-fast woman.
So, like, somebody's living in delusion.
I mean you sound like you're about 70 years old, so that's not my fault. You probably you know, whatever, but it's
That's the fucked up thing about this world. So what are you talking about?
In the open and you sound like you do that shit for fun you like it your husband likes it. He's a your husband is
So it is like you have I'm don't ask me for it
My pussy's not on the internet, but these cities are every day. I've seen you on the internet
Whatever they want to do in their relationship, you know, I'm saying
They don't have somebody that they can have fun with and have a good relationship with and have
About every day and go by hookers and go to the strip club by themselves instead of having a woman
That's gonna be on you. How do we buy hookers?
You made the claim
Yes, you're getting you know summer, you know for a fact you're more logical than that. How do I buy hookers go ahead?
I know that you're fucking being laying you guys are acting like you're fucking don't let the fuck you're talking about your husband
It is a cock and I've told you this I told you didn't want to debate now. We're gonna have one
That's why I told you to actually fucking makes like you some money
We're not know anything about anything my husband was laughing at you
Yeah, I missed your superhero. Yeah, he's laughing all the way to the cook
He's laughing when he's watching you get come in here
Hey, ghost, let's see him first of all have some fucking respect because they nobody do
it.
He's laughing.
Don't.
Why he's watching you get fucked.
My bad.
I'll ban you for 25.
Hey, one more time and I'll ban you off for 24 hours and I'll keep you gone for 24 hours
because what you won't do is disrespect me.
I'm a married woman ain't nobody trying to get here. I've got more money
I'm gonna $25 ban him for a fuck of 48 at 24 at 25
25 hour 25 dollars a guess what psyche go ahead summer good
Cuz you're either
So you're a trick just like I said
So go on you want to spend the rest of fucking money little bitch boy cuz you're do what you ain't get no pussy
But that's your problem. Who was that dude? Who was that dude helping me by the way cuz he did a good job, dude
Was that untouchable?
actually didn't say anything except about me wearing the fucking shirt you're
the one that's actually like you've never been in pussy before dude I'm just
waiting on this ghost guy to get banned but what happened was you don't have
more than me so you understand
If I sit in the 25 you will get fucking bad for 24 hours. So
Motherfucker just like I beat you to the punch last like that's why you didn't have your fucking panel because you didn't show up
So I grabbed that bitch
Psychi I'm sending you 25 right now because I already know what he's gonna try to do
Do you hear me yes
All right, okay, I'll take 24 for him
Yeah, I don't know what the big argument is
Me myself I've been married for 12 years and
Every time is a new time, you know what I mean because we have so much work to do
so when we when we find each other there there are no questions it might
even be weird but fuck everybody else because we're fucking each other
It's all about having fun, dude, and you know if you are lucky enough to have somebody that you can be friends with and you
Can be open with and I'm not neither one of us have to sneak around and do anything
My pussy ain't on the fucking internet. So what my fucking tits are guess a fuck dude
You think it bothers my husband? No my husband knew me when he met me
He knew I was exactly how I was just like I knew exactly how he was and we're lucky enough to be married to our best friend
So fuck anybody that has an issue with that
Yeah, I don't I don't even know why it's a discussion, but I don't either
But but you see people that they have nothing they have nothing in their lives
They don't even know how to have fun
Meanwhile people like us have been having our fun
Our entire lives, you know what I mean? Yeah
We've had some hard times and we've gone down some rough roads, but
Every single every single minute of it has been fun. Yeah, you should you shouldn't be showing your boobs all over the internet
I could do whatever I want. I'm grown right you're not my father
You don't pay my bills and you don't feed me fuck me or any of that. So you don't really get an opinion on what I do
I mean, you can say whatever
Your opinion don't hold any way
Of what I do, that's actually what I meant to say you can have your opinion on the husband
It's working all day long
And I and all you're doing is giving the money away to poor people you shouldn't be showing your boobs all day
I make my money to do the stuff that I do to help my community with so I can do whatever I want with my titties
Look, I work too hard to get my money away. I'm trying to buy a fucking other Rolex. I'm not playing with this shit
Know that's right. What's up random guy? Yeah, but you just wasted 25 bucks, man
I ain't said I ain't said it yet because I was waiting on him to try to do something
There's a bit smart money. I work hard for my money. It's mine. Oh, oh, I'm sorry
Random guy my random guys the guy on the side
Oh, I'm not your guy on the side. Don't don't pull me there your husband's listening
Yes, my husband here's everything
I mean I'm on vacation I don't care what anybody does. We're at right
Where you at, dude? I'm in Virginia. Who the fuck goes on vacation in Virginia?
Like I'd take you down
Those times now he just times me out fuck it else
start another one of my friend
I would take y'all down to the water, but I would lose my Wi-Fi
Virginia Beach
there's no signal out here
is that a Virginia Beach
no, I'm at a lake
oh
oh you're like a lake, I don't like the ocean
oh I love the ocean
Just thought this summer I
Mean
You don't need you don't always get to go where you love
But you know water water Virginia this year, huh? Who picked that was that you or is that your wife? I?
Mean it's where the what would you call it bang for the buck? Oh
You can't skip out on vacay. You can't skip on vacations. That's a team move fucking vacation fucking Virginia
Okay
It's okay. He wants to put me down for being on vacation. No, I've just said listen, dude
I'm in Pennsylvania. I know Virginia. I just like
It's not a place where people go. I just you don't hear it much. I don't know. That's all
Well, you can't Google it. It's it's called Smith Mountain. It's very popular
Really tomorrow at 1030
I'll be there
Hey man, as long as you're having fun, that's all that matters you having fun everyone check out sponkeys left tomorrow 1030
sponkeys channel again
So so as long as I'm having fun, but then yeah, you want to talk about the way other people live
So nah, it's just it's not like a popular spot to go on vacation. That's why you threw me off
That's all. Well, where would you go on vacation? Would you go to North Carolina? Maybe I don't know
Oh, you would go to North Carolina. Yeah over Virginia, of course
Hey, hey, hey homeboy. We left North Carolina to come to Virginia. So how about make any sense?
All right, you guys. I'm hopping off of here
You said I was a vacation shame you
You don't have you don't have an argument here
Oh, you don't I kind of did no you don't
Okay
How about go someplace outside of where you are? I didn't know you're from North Carolina
So that makes more sense. That's called the vacation when you leave where you are
Not exactly
Psyche how long are you gonna let these two rednecks argue? Yeah, we are rednecks. Listen to you motherfucker
To
Fucking biggest redneck selling purse. I've never heard this. Where are you from?
Cool, I say something I like that voice
Brave I'm just saying yeah, you two are fight you two are fighting like lovers. Yeah, I
Got my shirt off. I got my shirt off, too
Hey, where are you right now?
Huh who?
Random guy or a race ray one ray one. Oh
Call me a trans I don't have my glasses on my bed
Can't call you trans okay, don't worry
Right. Hey, you're calling trance. He better put his fucking glasses on before he speaks
That fucking sunburn face for you. What are you gonna do about it? Where are you? I'm on a phone
I'm just some random guy dude calm down
Well, I mean if you if you're gonna say somebody's not live in the right life like you would live it
You better give some very good examples about why you're so something you fucking team of vacationer
I'm just saying if you're gonna call somebody out
Yeah, you you better come up with something better and you and you better be there
Don't don't just say oh, I could do it better. Where are you right now?
I'm going to go back to the
Pretty
Sancti in Los Angeles. So in track will your bar you come back up. I ain't gonna pay just yet. I'll wait and I'll wait
Come on goes. Come on goes. You have some grace. I'm a pretty boy crying in the chat
How are you doing today like
No, I'm good. I woke up at like five in the afternoon and like I'm doing I'm doing pretty good summer
Good, I didn't make it. I didn't make it to you, right? I was gonna ask you next
I was part- I can't like you how he was doing
I got a new vacuum. I got this up T move for like 25 bucks. This is the vacuum cleaner. It's like, you know
Kind of like a smaller vacuum, but should be pretty good. Oh my god. Are you gay? Are you gay psyche? Are you gay? Yeah? Yeah
No
Yeah
Hello
Hello, we lose Ray. We lost Ray. No, yeah, I'm still here. Oh, oh, he's already lost
Ray how was your day? No, he's shot. Oh, well, it was a pretty good one
All right, I got a vacuum cleaner. Are you ready to my vacuum?
Are you retired too Ray? Yeah, I sure you're a vacuum psyche. It's your show. Yeah. I saw summer summer. I paid
$550 for a vacuum cleaner from Best Buy today
Alrighty
G1 I was your date random. I made some money. It's good
new person say your name
Okay, yes me. Yeah. Oh
This guy again, I had a good day and Jack up. How was your day? I
I did a bunch of swimming in the lake and
caught a bunch of Sun and
Can't nobody pull me down. Oh, no
Oh, no right now
Your face is already growing back your hair goes so fast
All right, I think oh J1 zoo. I don't want anybody be left out J1. How was your day?
Okay, okay. I can ask this is some more question
Not unless you're gonna tell us what happened in New York today
What the shooting? I mean
I think what's a guy enter a building with a AK?
So you are or AR AR 15
So so what part of New York do you stay in?
Talk about the
So the guy George supposedly maybe it looks like the guy may have drove from Las Vegas and he unalived
Cop and couple other people and then himself
Yeah, and actually I stayed in the hotel that was right across the street the last time I was in New York
That was I can't say the name now, but I forget it, but yeah, I stayed at that hotel
The marry at my hotel
No
The trip the triple tree the triple tree and slack my dick. How about that don't make fun of me Sutter
Oh, okay, so I can ask mr. Summer quick question. Let's have a look right. I
Don't think I asked him this question before I think I asked Jack Spade this question, but I want to know his opinion on electric trucks
That's kind of good. That's not kind of the new thing now. No, if you drive in a lecture if you drive anything less than a
Summer because he's got big tits now, I guess
Ray one's got big titties. So let's let ray one answer the question. Go ahead ray one
No, no, no, do you drive a v8 a man drive v8 to me, but
You I guess your name is summer now. So you got big tits in your loud. So go for it. Fuck a VA get diesel idiot
How this motherfuckers copying my name?
Ask me a question not you ray one and his name has been that name forever
We've had this discussion already. What the fuck and it's not your name. It's J1 and ray one
plus
Red next dude
I
Know everybody's everybody is over
Answer the question
Because she does no shit about vehicles then we'll move forward. Okay
That's right because I was gonna say ask dick to fucking go
J1 why are you a man J1?
Yes one question, can you give him some respect what the fuck you're such a dick right? Oh my god. He's gone now
Why are you gonna be a bully on panel ray one yelling at one question and not even to you
He came up here and asked why can't you drive a remote control question a remote control truck
You fucking serious a remote control truck
Well Billy are you
He's got a voice changer. This ain't real. This ain't real fucking voice changer. No, she's from Kentucky. Yeah, she's a she's a hit too
I said, that's not real. I'm a lot smarter than you are because when somebody asks me a fucking question
I like to answer it. Not right one. Nobody fucking talks. It's a fake voice. He's trolling us
No, no, no
It's not it's not a fake voice box. I agree with you random. Definitely not really fun
Definitely something right now summer. I'm gonna ask you something right now
you ready
We're waiting
How damn I
Know you have a heart and you did you're a good woman, but what do you think you're accomplishing going out there with all those?
Those people and wasting your time on them. Hold on. Hold on. What's up summer? What's up, everybody? What's up, son?
I got a joke for that one that guy that was up for I don't want what's his name?
When
Okay, I got okay not not
He's not here though
My shit up man
Now don't worry about
Who's this one of the boys from the hood?
It's a joke on the ass up. I get the troll in your bitch ass
Came to troll motherfucker, you know, we don't want to get troll get the fuck off the panel. That's what I came to do
All right one wants to play so you should play with him and I don't play with growing man. I'm out peace
There's no way Ray won's voice. That's definitely gone. Whoa. Where did it go?
You ain't doing this no more
I was about to slam duck. It's watermelon head. Yeah, you had to type it in your fucking voice changer. Whatever. All right
See the delay he's delayed
Yeah, no, but some summer summer summer. What do you think you're doing with these people?
What people right one?
I mean, these people, these people under the interstates, under the over bridges.
But what do you think? What do you think I'm doing with those people?
What are you laughing about? It's like, I don't know.
Are you sure you're not just making yourself feel good?
I think you have a hard I think you have a hard you're a good woman but yeah, but okay, I'll just shut up
Yeah, put another to ask your question or something like everybody's question keeps getting stopped in the middle of it
Can we we have like one complete question and answer?
Yeah, the cyber truck has more it has more torque than the regular trucks like diesel trucks, too
But I wouldn't buy a cyber truck
But technically I think they have more torque
That was the question
But I do like the new
Teslas or whatever those kind of cute and I like the white ones. Those are nice
I'm not a fan of the lunches, but I know that they I mean physics and they have more torque
They just you can't deny that
Yeah, but for how long that's a good question to I don't fucking know I don't mess with them I wouldn't buy one
Okay, well, that's pretty fascinating. I don't drive so
You don't drive? No, I mean I have before you know, I drove for several years
But I have a bike now, but it's just a miss waiting to my neighbor said they're gonna fix it. So
But they just move so I'm waiting for them to
Pick up I mean, I have a 20 year old Camry and
It handles business, you know what I'm saying
Yeah, can't oh camera. I drove a camera before I had my grandmother's Camry. I
Unfortunately not for very long, but older cameras are sick. I like them. It's a 20 year old Camry. That's badass
Camry's are good cars
Yeah, we you gonna shame me for that
No, we drive my mom sold a Camry 15 years ago, dude
Yeah, to me I scrapped it across the fucking thing
So pretty people in the chat hey shout out to everybody in the chat, you know
You just like this dream. I appreciate that go ahead. I'm sorry
So this guy's supposed to be some army guy and he's driving a 20 year old Camry
Yeah, and this guy is supposed to be ray one and he
He's a worthless son of a bitch that just follows people around and shames them
Well, this is definitely the redneck stream. I like it. Hey, what do you drive Ray? What kind of trucks you got?
So, so I'm currently I just purchased a
GMC Sierra
1500 dishes. Oh
expedition
Yeah, what engine the Godzilla?
a VA
what engine is it
what's how many liters
I don't keep up with all that shit
you're a fucking, you're a lying piece of shit
right, sounds like a liar to me
what the fuck is that?
cause I don't know the engine size
yeah you idiot
exactly why
100%
Mean what your cars engine size you fuck you sucker right six seven power show bitch
Stop fucking gasser. I'll stomp on your gasser. You won't be a redneck stream. I got my fucking chewing. Let's go
You like this psyche or you're gonna keep you're gonna boot me. What am I?
Yeah, pussy. We got a gas fucking truck and no you you'll notice summer is showing her tits as soon as I said the truck I own I
Mean but you don't know anything about the truck you own and that's by your own admission
Not a mechanic on trackable
As soon as you said 20 25, I knew your broke ass was lying, okay?
Because I traded in my 20
Shit, I traded in my
for
$25,000 peckerhead
Peckerhead Wow, what kind of vulgar language? Yeah, I like her head. I cannot believe it
What vehicle was that sir?
I have a 24 team GM Sierra I always buy GMC I've had luck with them since I was in my late 20s.
Yeah, sounds good.
Sounds good brother.
Hey, my phone is falling.
What was that?
Hey, you got a truck.
Okay, so it's a fucking
Expedition yeah, yeah, I got a truck. I mean I could
So the whole thing I could drive summer around places y'all couldn't
Couldn't even a whole fucking couch in your fucking
Fake-ass trucks. I have a real truck. It's an expedition
The fuck are you talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about boy?
What are you talking about? Oh, we call in each other boy now. All right. Yeah, boy
Go boys, you know, I have never saw a summer with her husband
So so I'm just gonna go out on a limb and say
She's lying about that
Yeah, I am
I mean, are you lying about your truck?
I'm not either. No. Whoa when I drive across your face on trackable. You ask
Inbred hillbilly, shut the fuck up. I'm not inbred. I've already showed
It's not a truck you dickhead you came in a whole fucking couch
some are those I don't owe anybody anybody in the receipts anymore
I owe you right over my head before I body slam you down
she can't be married
fuck out of here
why don't you show your fat husband
summer
Love big men little women usually do like big men six foot five baby. Yep. All of it love all of it
Let me see your expedition
Yeah, let's see your expedition bitch. Yeah, you're gonna buy a fucking trailer the whole account you fucking loser. I
Mean I would show you guys the lake, but it's it's
Where's your wife at?
My wife said I had a wife
Not you untrackable. I you're beautiful wonderful amazing wife is amazing this loser this since he wants to keep talking about my husband
Where's your where's your girlfriend? Where's your female in your life? I?
Got two or three girlfriends. I think this whole argument is disgusting. I think this whole argument is disgusting
That's just my opinion
Which one
It's all just dumb shit.
Like we could be talking about weed.
Are you gonna let her sit up here and calm her hair
and calm her hair and print a round psych
and then say she has a husband?
In front of all these men.
That's goddamn fucking bullshit.
It's got nothing to let me comb my hair. Hold on. Wait a minute. Let me get it
Good, I didn't know coming my hair would bother somebody but I'm gonna bother you had coming you're you said coming your hair
Yeah, he said coming
She's saying she has a husband and she's basically spreading her ash cheeks in front of everybody
I'm just saying it's a hell of a thing when you have so much to say about other people, but you never present yourself
I
Never seen that mean either
But I'm over here brushing my hair I'm combing my hair and bothers people I
Mean
Summer see me take my daughter for a walk
Some summer see me do so many things
My god, get the fuck out of here on track.
I would punch you in your fucking face so hard, boy.
You hear me on track?
I hear you, and I'm so scared.
Shaking in our britches.
I need to get this guy's AI voice chat. It's funny.
Right?
It's great.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't think there's anybody out there like that, so
well look what she's doing, look what she's doing right now, psych
well, look who's not having fun
it's you, sir
she's combing her hair wet
it's good to brush your hair like a hundred times
like I said, I'm at the lake and someone's brushing her hair
She's
Lording her hair over all men
Yeah, and I
Just just like I would brush my daughter's hair
She's she is doing the woman's thing and and brushing her hair. Do you have a problem with that?
But the whole thing is all she could get all the whole thing is all she could get is the
350 pound
Black man. It's all she ever had
350 pounds, but he is a black man
Are you are you jealous? Sounds like it, right?
That sounds like jealousy to me
Yeah
They're getting me
Not much of a Christian, but that sounds like a bit of a sin thinking that you can have something that you don't deserve
Hey, whether I was with him
You would stand a chance, right? You would stand a chance to drink of my fucking piss water
So summer wastes all her time and day on losers
What she does
Yeah, well you waste all your time telling other people how to live, right?
Are you a trick that I put us off a long time ago or something? Why are you so butt-hurt little boy?
I mean
Feel but hurt about what you have to say are we supposed to change our lives because you have something to say
Who are you intractable
Who am I? I mean, I could be your daddy. You just don't know
See, I'm swing swing right now with my shirt off enjoying the life
He sees another cat or she sees you the cat. She's like, hey, she's like, who's that pretty lady?
So I don't want to be on camera right now mom
Oh, but you don't like cigarette smokers. Yeah. Yeah, but the whole thing is the whole thing is you will always see summer's body, but you'll never see her husband. You never will.
My husband was just on panel with us talking. So what are you talking about and actually they have my husband has been on panel
He's kissed me on the forehead while we've been on panel talking to psyche. So I don't
Hey, wait, how is the person that won't show their camera gonna call somebody else out for not being on camera?
I've been on camera for two
For two and a half years now. I don't give a shit about showing my face because everything I do is true
Well, I mean you look like shit you you look like shit
You look like shit. It couldn't get any worse
Next man does with his wife or whatever
Look how ugly he is look how ugly he is
I mean, I thank you. I thank you pretty summer, but yeah, I don't understand your attitude
I've even exercised in what about your attitude boy. Oh
Shit, who just said that?
This is this is a stargazer stargazers here stargazer
Yes, I just walked into the conversation. Let me tell you something boy
Yeah, you get the fucking shit out of your mouth before you speak to me woman
Get the shit out of your mouth before you use you need to learn
Now you don't talk to me like that boy. Great one. Turn your camera on bitch
Turn your camera on
Come on, I'm gonna listen to your fucking mouth for almost 30 minutes. Now, I'm up here
Mr. One is willing to do a push-up kind contest
He's gonna have to do he's gonna have to put his camera on
He's gonna have to
Come on. I've heard you run your cloud-ass mouth for long enough
came up. Oh
You want to run my sister down?
You don't know who her husband is cuz I did
Star Stargaze Stargaze, where are you from, Mississippi white whore?
I will set my camera and you will not beat me. I wear ass mother fucker
You have just about done it right then. Hell. I'm about to do it without you
He's he is a complete and sell girl
You know
Oh, come on
She says I meant she says so though she says I'm in sale, but she wants me
No, honey, she don't want you. You ain't nothing but a peon to her
You're a fucking peon. I know that she can piss on. Do you understand that a peon? You're a delusion on
She wants me over that 50 year old black husband of hers
You wish
You bet you sound like you wet my husband's dick. That's what it sounds like. It sounds like you're fetched away with that big black dick
You want some of it, right?
It sounds like it does
No words now big black cock got your mouth
Oh, here you go push ups. Okay. Here we go. Look at trackable. It's gonna do something
There goes my little bro, come on bud
All right, well, let's see you do some of this. We'll see you what I do what I'm trackable is doing right now
Great ones. I still has his camera off
Of course he does this, he's a puppy.
My God, it took everything you had to do one.
I mean, he is kind of shaking.
I
Would knock that motherfucker out
He's right she wants him to leave you damn right
Look he was kidding he was kidding
Same going the whole way down
There we go. That's good. That's six
Okay, so very red
Who's gonna God Jesus he doesn't even have any hair on top of his head
All I got to do is one and I'll be you all I got to do is one and I'll be you right
I'm so you nasty you you nasty bald-headed fucker
You couldn't even do 10 push-ups. Well, my face thinks he's cute. So is anybody think you're cute? Probably not
He's got my flip luscious
Oh now and now he's gonna show us a little three
Oh my god, oh my god
That now he's flirt now. He's flirting with psych
There you go, oh, yeah, how many of those can you do right?
Probably 200
Probably
Yeah, exactly
Like I said, I've been listening for a while
He just likes to hear. He likes to hear his. Why don't you? Why don't you shut up and and don't listen to me. You know, it's the
charity work of the night. We got to make him feel like he actually matters, you know. Yeah, he thinks he matters and
don't know who is that nosy woman in the bottom left hand corner? Who is our nosy? That's your sister. Yep,
Who's that redneck loser that uh, can't prove shit? Who's the one it won't came up improve
Untrackable me and you summer psyche. There's summer
Hey, no no offense to too many of y'all but
I was born to hurt feelings and
I
Mostly hurt my own
but
All this shit talk
You don't you don't you couldn't hold sweat to me, bro
You couldn't even do 10 push-ups boy
You couldn't even do 10 push-ups and and you couldn't even show up to the fight. Could you?
You couldn't you couldn't show up to your own wedding. You son of a bitch
Yeah, because I want to put you
I want to put you in a head
I want to put you in a headlock and rub your face in the ground boy
You you couldn't show up to the birth of your own child. You that's how much of a loser you are
You you want me to hurt your feelings I don't have to
I don't I don't have to
I've been swimming for three hours today, and that's not an excuse but I
Have yet to see you even dick dip your head in the water
You you need to go underwater you need to go underwater for more than three hours
Couldn't hang you couldn't hang with me
You couldn't hang with me, bro
You couldn't do it. I
Don't think anybody up here could
And and that's not a child
It's not a child. Oh
You fucking serious
You fucking idiot
Well, what are you showing?
Let's go. You're all talk. You're just a talk of bubble right now. Do something. I will I'll go get the lantern and
And I'll go swim for a little bit
Loser got kicked out. He got kicked out of the army summer
This fucking idiot got kicked out of the army. You understand that I
Got kicked out of what?
He didn't get kicked out of the army. What do you talk? I know Unchalkable. What are you talking about, dude?
Got kicked out of what a couple years now. No, he got kicked out of army
He got kicked out of army for being a loser. He couldn't do anything
Now I might have been a cook but I did not get kicked out and you can't prove anything and you can't you certainly can't
You you can't stand up why would you think you could hang with me, bro?
There you go, you can't stand up here. Why would you why would you my father right some more?
I'm just pressure my hair you all because it really bothers you right for some reason
I'm just you pickable you look you're looking really hot summer
Good, I'm confused about this guy
He's a yeah
He loves to hate me what happens? I don't hate you, but I don't hate you
I mean, I've never been in prison
Hate is the same like you know love to hate not I'm not saying you hate me
I've never been to prison, but I would definitely fuck this
If I
Hey, hey you fucking faggot if I could get my hands on you in prison you wouldn't be here today
You understand that boy
Good look. Oh, so now we know he's been in prison by the way, he just said that untrackable think about that one
Yeah, well, I was an LTI I was an LTI when I was 14 years old was
What the hell's LTI?
And you were 14 years old
I'm pretty I'm pretty sure there's some statutory charges that are gonna come from that
Yeah, but yeah, what what about your face?
Yeah, what about my face?
Go ahead compare your face everyone. That's what I thought bitch
The neighbors can hear what I'm saying
But they can also hear what you're saying to yeah, because you have you have thin wall apartments
You have thin wall apartments
Untrackable. I'm sitting outside
Isn't it is
He's on vacation right now Simon is his house not even look at the cameras
He keeps telling try not bald-headed, but he's not looking that that's not even an apartment. He's on a Timu vacation in Virginia
Yeah, I'm on a Timu vacation in Virginia with a lake with a big-ass lake
I got her. I mean it looks like it looks like you go out. It looks like you go outside with a pair of
binoculars on your face
Undraggable
There we go
What's up random guy, how you doing I'm doing all right I
Got I got the bugs and the frogs
Parking at me
God imagine no, so
Imagine nobody talking to you and you still got to run your goddamn mouth
Imagine that imagine
Imagine your own people that, you know, have done something.
No, no, no, no, shut up, Baggett.
I'm talking about that creature in the right hand corner.
That thing in the right hand corner, I'm saying imagine.
Oh, so you think you run the show now?
Go ahead, run the show with your little purple circle.
Go ahead run the show
You are a loser untrackable. You probably don't even have $100 to your name. Oh
Money is worthless
What does money have to do with anything?
That means a lot
What it means a lot to somebody that doesn't have anything that can't take a fucking vacation because they're too busy sucking dick
But you're the only dick sucker around here boy. No, I think you are
No, it's like here too
Please
Summer and summer and stargazing probably I'm not sure I mean, yeah, I gladly I
Mean been there done that
right
They start to prove it I
Will never understand the troll game. I will never understand it
Well, there's fun a reaction they go off to get fuel from getting a reaction to their shit
And so they'll just keep going if they don't get a reaction
I'll move on to somebody else. No, no thing is psyche
He thought he was gonna shave his beard and come up here and get some pussy or something
What do you thought?
Well, you know, he maybe he might be able to I don't know. He's a very attractive man
He was an army captain. I think he has a wife. So I don't think he's really trying to do that
Do you think he's a tractor?
Yeah, he's a very nice looking man. Well, well you you and him going to date you and him
Yeah, he's not he's not he's not gay and second of all he has a wife the third of all. He's not really my
He is definitely gay, that guy is gay.
Why is he not your type, Shike?
There's nothing wrong with him.
He's married.
But you already said that, it was like one point.
Then you made him not being your type a whole other point.
Can we end that?
He's a fucking redneck?
I mentioned Latino guys with tattoos.
Pretty much.
So you so you think it so you think untrackable isn't gay. Look at it. Okay. I
See him don't think he's gay. He looks very masculine. So that's why you let auto up, huh?
That's why I did well. I think he was kind of cute
But now he's like he's like getting flirty diamonds. So he's off the market. I think wait is full of flirty diamond actually a trans
Yeah
Okay, so he's in the trans so
Yeah, he might be into you
I'm not really interested. Oh, no, a flurry diamond was dating untrackable
She was
Yeah, untrackable. Is that true? I
Would love the receipts on that. Okay. Anybody got receipts on that one. I want to see
This is 30 diamond. I'm talking to you in an intracable DM's. I don't know. I don't believe it. I can't believe it
I think that intracable. I don't think there'll be any to be found. Do you?
Be hard to find something can't be found
He's a very bad at trolling he's like it's funny
Is a beautiful person
That's nice. It's nice even say it has been hilarious
Yeah, yeah, I hope you guys are having a fun night
Right in here and that he thinks he's got
Yeah, his shining personality is just oh
And it's really bright dull black
Yeah, the only proceeds I bring is that if you think you're gonna hurt my feelings
Yeah, you got a long way to go, brother. I
Just remember the funniest thing is like the first time
Summer summer is really something she she's
She's a beautiful lady. She has a heart. I can't believe how she's letting these homeless people take advantage of her
How do you mean I don't think she is she's helping people of her own free will and what?
How are they taking advantage of me great one?
They probably laugh at you when you go away
They say we got that white we got that white woman again. We got her again. I don't think so. I
Think they're very grateful
Definitely have some underlying problems though raise down in Mississippi next to the ocean
No, I know people I know people worse than she does she's Kentucky. I'm Mississippi. I know people
Yeah, Ray, what do you what do you call um
You said something really offensive to stargazer. I think that was kind of rude of you. What do you say to her?
You remind you remind me
Now you said something to stargazer. I forget what you said. I
Don't know. She is she fat or something. Is she fat? I don't know
Right, are you black?
Ray Ray. Are you black? I
I am a Caucasian man the Caucasian
Get the cuckoo cock out of your mouth and talk your stargazer you're still here. Yes, okay. What what the fuck did this guy save you?
Oh, he's just been concoctedly rude and mean for him to.
He called you, he called you something, I forget.
No, no, no, no, no.
Summer is, summer is raising hell in all of Kentucky.
They can't, the law officials, the cops, the judges,
the police can't do anything without summer getting all up in it.
Sure, I will
Only when they're doing well, I praise the ones that are doing good
So I'm not anti-caught by any way should perform
Yeah, summer's an amazing
Look at that. Well, where's your husband at summer?
You're pretty worried about him, so he must be with you
Ray is he with you tell summer it's time for husband is time to go home
You know I would I would punch her husband right in the face, you know that why are you threatening physical violence? No, no, don't say that
No, she's asking for it. She's she's asking for summer that she she's so on her stuff
She's
No, she's bored with her. She's bored with him. She's bored
Me my husband had a lot of fun right before I came on panel not bored with him at all. I put him to sleep
That's what I did. I was a good wife
Because he don't have a good wife
He's got to get up and go to work a little bit I put him to bed I fed him I fucked him and he went to sleep
Ray what do you think?
I mean, is she
What it's like
Lou
I'll be that kind of good wife. I said wait a second my phone
He worked a hard day I fed him a bussy and he went to bed. What else does a man want?
Yeah, sounds pretty ideal. What do you think Ray?
Okay, well, I think I might end around 11 o'clock. Let's see what time. Oh, it's already 11
Well, what do you guys think? Is anybody wanna?
If you're tired, it's our live. Yeah, so live and I think yeah, we'll see what else is live and
Love you guys. Thank you. I'm like
Is anybody else live you guys see? I think I think I think beta is live. So maybe we'll go to beat is to or
Okay, yeah, we go to be ready. I think I heard beat is live and then maybe summer will be so
You know, let's all support each other. Thank you guys. I had a great night. Love you and I might be on
Love you. Talk to you soon guys. It was fun. Bye. Love you summer